<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Skills.sh Feed</title>
        <link>https://skills.sh</link>
        <description>Latest skill data from skills.sh</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Daily] Skills.sh snapshot (2026-02-22)]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:snapshot</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Daily snapshot.
Providers: skills.sh
All Time skills: 33632
Trending skills: 12768
Hot skills: 1270
Top All Time: find-skills (286338)
Top Trending: agent-tools (8809)
Top Hot: remotion-render (316)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#17): mcp-builder]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/anthropics/skills/mcp-builder</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:anthropics/skills/mcp-builder</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #17
Installs: 17
Source: anthropics/skills
Description: Guide for creating high-quality MCP (Model Context Protocol) servers that enable LLMs to interact with external services through well-designed tools. Use when building MCP servers to integrate external APIs or services, whether in Python (FastMCP) or Node/TypeScript (MCP SDK).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#18): seo-content-brief]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/seo-content-brief</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/seo-content-brief</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #18
Installs: 10
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: SEO content brief creation with keyword research, search intent analysis, and content structure. Covers SERP analysis, heading hierarchy, word count targets, and internal linking strategy. Use for: content briefs, SEO writing, blog strategy, content planning, keyword targeting. Triggers: seo content brief, content brief, seo brief, keyword research, search intent, content strategy, blog brief, seo writing, content planning, keyword targeting, serp analysis, content outline, seo article, blog seo]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#19): python-executor]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/python-executor</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/python-executor</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #19
Installs: 10
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Execute Python code in a safe sandboxed environment via [inference.sh](https://inference.sh). Pre-installed: NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib, requests, BeautifulSoup, Selenium, Playwright, MoviePy, Pillow, OpenCV, trimesh, and 100+ more libraries. Use for: data processing, web scraping, image manipulation, video creation, 3D model processing, PDF generation, API calls, automation scripts. Triggers: python, execute code, run script, web scraping, data analysis, image processing, video editing, 3D models, automation, pandas, matplotlib]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#23): product-photography]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/product-photography</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/product-photography</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #23
Installs: 10
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: AI product photography with studio lighting, lifestyle shots, and packshot conventions. Covers angles, backgrounds, shadow types, hero shots, and e-commerce image requirements. Use for: product photos, e-commerce images, Amazon listings, packshots, lifestyle photography. Triggers: product photography, product photo, packshot, e-commerce photography, product shot, product image, studio photography, lifestyle product, amazon product photo, product listing image, hero shot, product mockup, commercial photography]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#24): image-to-video]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/image-to-video</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/image-to-video</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #24
Installs: 10
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Still-to-video conversion guide: model selection, motion prompting, and camera movement. Covers Wan 2.5 i2v, Seedance, Fabric, Grok Video with when to use each. Use for: animating images, creating video from stills, adding motion, product animations. Triggers: image to video, i2v, animate image, still to video, add motion to image, image animation, photo to video, animate still, wan i2v, image2video, bring image to life, animate photo, motion from image]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#27): ui-ux-pro-max]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/nextlevelbuilder/ui-ux-pro-max-skill/ui-ux-pro-max</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:nextlevelbuilder/ui-ux-pro-max-skill/ui-ux-pro-max</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #27
Installs: 38
Source: nextlevelbuilder/ui-ux-pro-max-skill
Description: UI/UX design intelligence. 50 styles, 21 palettes, 50 font pairings, 20 charts, 9 stacks (React, Next.js, Vue, Svelte, SwiftUI, React Native, Flutter, Tailwind, shadcn/ui). Actions: plan, build, create, design, implement, review, fix, improve, optimize, enhance, refactor, check UI/UX code. Projects: website, landing page, dashboard, admin panel, e-commerce, SaaS, portfolio, blog, mobile app, .html, .tsx, .vue, .svelte. Elements: button, modal, navbar, sidebar, card, table, form, chart. Styles: glassmorphism, claymorphism, minimalism, brutalism, neumorphism, bento grid, dark mode, responsive, skeuomorphism, flat design. Topics: color palette, accessibility, animation, layout, typography, font pairing, spacing, hover, shadow, gradient. Integrations: shadcn/ui MCP for component search and examples.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#28): better-auth-best-practices]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/better-auth/skills/better-auth-best-practices</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:better-auth/skills/better-auth-best-practices</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #28
Installs: 15
Source: better-auth/skills
Description: Skill for integrating Better Auth - the comprehensive TypeScript authentication framework.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#29): case-study-writing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/case-study-writing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/case-study-writing</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #29
Installs: 9
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: B2B case study writing with STAR framework, data visualization, and research. Covers structure, customer quotes, metrics presentation, and distribution formats. Use for: customer success stories, portfolio pieces, sales enablement, marketing content. Triggers: case study, customer story, success story, b2b case study, client testimonial, customer case study, portfolio case study, use case, customer win, results story]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#30): video-ad-specs]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/video-ad-specs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/video-ad-specs</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #30
Installs: 9
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Video ad creation with exact platform-specific specs for TikTok, Instagram, YouTube, Facebook, LinkedIn. Covers dimensions, duration limits, AIDA framework, and caption requirements. Use for: video ads, social media ads, paid media creative, video marketing, ad production. Triggers: video ad, social media ad, tiktok ad, instagram ad, youtube ad, facebook ad, linkedin ad, video creative, ad specs, paid media, video marketing, ad production, reels ad, stories ad, pre roll, bumper ad]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#31): image-upscaling]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/image-upscaling</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/image-upscaling</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #31
Installs: 9
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Upscale and enhance images with Real-ESRGAN, Thera, Topaz, FLUX Upscaler via inference.sh CLI. Models: Real-ESRGAN, Thera (any size), FLUX Dev Upscaler, Topaz Image Upscaler. Use for: enhance low-res images, upscale AI art, restore old photos, increase resolution. Triggers: upscale image, image upscaler, enhance image, increase resolution, real esrgan, ai upscale, super resolution, image enhancement, upscaling, enlarge image, higher resolution, 4k upscale, hd upscale]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#34): customer-persona]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/customer-persona</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/customer-persona</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #34
Installs: 9
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Research-backed customer persona creation with market data and avatar generation. Covers demographics, psychographics, jobs-to-be-done, journey mapping, and anti-personas. Use for: marketing strategy, product development, UX research, sales enablement, content strategy. Triggers: customer persona, buyer persona, user persona, target audience, ideal customer, customer profile, audience research, user research, icp, ideal customer profile, target market, customer avatar, audience persona]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#36): create-auth-skill]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/better-auth/skills/create-auth-skill</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:better-auth/skills/create-auth-skill</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #36
Installs: 9
Source: better-auth/skills
Description: Skill for creating auth layers in TypeScript/JavaScript apps using Better Auth.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#38): fix]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/facebook/react/fix</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:facebook/react/fix</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #38
Installs: 8
Source: facebook/react
Description: Use when you have lint errors, formatting issues, or before committing code to ensure it passes CI.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#40): linkedin-content]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/linkedin-content</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/linkedin-content</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #40
Installs: 8
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: LinkedIn post writing with hook formulas, formatting rules, and engagement patterns. Covers post types, algorithm signals, character limits, and content pillars. Use for: LinkedIn posts, professional content, thought leadership, B2B content, personal branding. Triggers: linkedin post, linkedin content, linkedin writing, linkedin strategy, linkedin engagement, linkedin algorithm, linkedin hook, linkedin formatting, thought leadership, professional content, b2b content, linkedin growth]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#42): press-release-writing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/press-release-writing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/press-release-writing</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #42
Installs: 8
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Press release writing in AP style with inverted pyramid structure. Covers formatting, datelines, quotes, boilerplates, and fact-checking. Use for: product launches, funding announcements, partnerships, company news, events. Triggers: press release, pr writing, media release, news release, announcement, product launch announcement, funding announcement, company news, media advisory, ap style, press statement, news wire]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#47): pdf]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/anthropics/skills/pdf</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:anthropics/skills/pdf</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #47
Installs: 22
Source: anthropics/skills
Description: Comprehensive PDF manipulation toolkit for extracting text and tables, creating new PDFs, merging/splitting documents, and handling forms. When Claude needs to fill in a PDF form or programmatically process, generate, or analyze PDF documents at scale.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#48): brand-guidelines]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/anthropics/skills/brand-guidelines</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:anthropics/skills/brand-guidelines</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #48
Installs: 10
Source: anthropics/skills
Description: Applies Anthropic's official brand colors and typography to any sort of artifact that may benefit from having Anthropic's look-and-feel. Use it when brand colors or style guidelines, visual formatting, or company design standards apply.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#50): email-and-password-best-practices]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/better-auth/skills/email-and-password-best-practices</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:better-auth/skills/email-and-password-best-practices</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #50
Installs: 7
Source: better-auth/skills
Description: This skill provides guidance and enforcement rules for implementing secure email and password authentication using Better Auth.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#7): logo-design-guide]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/logo-design-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-6/skills/logo-design-guide</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #7
Installs: 16
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Logo design principles and AI image generation best practices for creating logos. Covers logo types, prompting techniques, scalability rules, and iteration workflows. Use for: brand identity, startup logos, app icons, favicons, logo concepts. Triggers: logo design, create logo, brand logo, logo generation, ai logo, logo maker, icon design, brand mark, logo concept, startup logo, app icon logo]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#46): agent-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/agent-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topTrending:new:inference-sh-6/skills/agent-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #46
Installs: 385
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: name: agent-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#48): web-search]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/web-search</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topTrending:new:inference-sh-6/skills/web-search</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #48
Installs: 380
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Web search and content extraction with Tavily and Exa via inference.sh CLI. Apps: Tavily Search, Tavily Extract, Exa Search, Exa Answer, Exa Extract. Capabilities: AI-powered search, content extraction, direct answers, research. Use for: research, RAG pipelines, fact-checking, content aggregation, agents. Triggers: web search, tavily, exa, search api, content extraction, research, internet search, ai search, search assistant, web scraping, rag, perplexity alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank down (16 → 34): pdf]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/anthropics/skills/pdf</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topAllTime:rank:anthropics/skills/pdf</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #16
Current rank: #34
Delta: -18
Installs: 18566 (prev 18415)
Source: anthropics/skills
Description: Comprehensive PDF manipulation toolkit for extracting text and tables, creating new PDFs, merging/splitting documents, and handling forms. When Claude needs to fill in a PDF form or programmatically process, generate, or analyze PDF documents at scale.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank up (21 → 18): azure-ai]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-ai</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topAllTime:rank:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #21
Current rank: #18
Delta: +3
Installs: 19411 (prev 18181)
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Use for Azure AI: Search, Speech, OpenAI, Document Intelligence. Helps with search, vector/hybrid search, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, transcription, OCR. USE FOR: AI Search, query search, vector search, hybrid search, semantic search, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, transcribe, OCR, convert text to speech. DO NOT USE FOR: Function apps/Functions (use azure-functions), databases (azure-postgres/azure-kusto), general Azure resources.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (10 → 35): newsletter-curation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/newsletter-curation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/newsletter-curation</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #10
Current rank: #35
Delta: -25
Installs: 9 (prev 23)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Newsletter curation with content sourcing, editorial structure, and subscriber growth strategies. Covers issue formatting, link roundups, commentary style, and sending cadence. Use for: email newsletters, link roundups, weekly digests, curated content, creator newsletters. Triggers: newsletter, email newsletter, newsletter curation, weekly digest, link roundup, curated newsletter, newsletter writing, newsletter format, subscriber growth, newsletter strategy, content curation, newsletter template]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (11 → 49): competitor-teardown]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/competitor-teardown</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/competitor-teardown</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #11
Current rank: #49
Delta: -38
Installs: 7 (prev 23)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Structured competitive analysis with feature matrices, SWOT, positioning maps, and UX review. Covers research frameworks, pricing comparison, review mining, and visual deliverables. Use for: market research, competitive intelligence, investor decks, product strategy, sales enablement. Triggers: competitor analysis, competitive analysis, competitor teardown, market research, competitive intelligence, swot analysis, competitor comparison, market landscape, competitor review, competitive landscape, feature comparison, market positioning]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (12 → 43): dialogue-audio]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/dialogue-audio</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/dialogue-audio</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #12
Current rank: #43
Delta: -31
Installs: 8 (prev 22)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Multi-speaker dialogue audio creation with Dia TTS. Covers speaker tags, emotion control, pacing, conversation flow, and post-production. Use for: podcasts, audiobooks, explainers, character dialogue, conversational content. Triggers: dialogue audio, multi speaker, conversation audio, dia tts, two speakers, podcast audio, character voices, voice acting, dialogue generation, conversation tts, multi voice, speaker tags, dialogue recording]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (13 → 44): tools-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/tools-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/tools-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #13
Current rank: #44
Delta: -31
Installs: 8 (prev 21)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: name: tools-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (14 → 41): widgets-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/widgets-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/widgets-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #14
Current rank: #41
Delta: -27
Installs: 8 (prev 21)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: name: widgets-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (16 → 39): og-image-design]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/og-image-design</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/og-image-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #16
Current rank: #39
Delta: -23
Installs: 8 (prev 19)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Open Graph and social sharing image design with platform specs, text placement, and branding. Covers OG meta tags, Twitter cards, LinkedIn previews, and dynamic generation. Use for: social sharing images, blog thumbnails, link previews, social cards. Triggers: og image, open graph, social sharing image, twitter card, social card, link preview image, og meta, sharing preview, social thumbnail, meta image, og:image, twitter:image, linkedin preview]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (17 → 20): agent-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/agent-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/agent-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #17
Current rank: #20
Delta: -3
Installs: 10 (prev 19)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: name: agent-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (21 → 46): web-search]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/web-search</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/web-search</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #21
Current rank: #46
Delta: -25
Installs: 8 (prev 18)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Web search and content extraction with Tavily and Exa via inference.sh CLI. Apps: Tavily Search, Tavily Extract, Exa Search, Exa Answer, Exa Extract. Capabilities: AI-powered search, content extraction, direct answers, research. Use for: research, RAG pipelines, fact-checking, content aggregation, agents. Triggers: web search, tavily, exa, search api, content extraction, research, internet search, ai search, search assistant, web scraping, rag, perplexity alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (22 → 37): explainer-video-guide]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/explainer-video-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/explainer-video-guide</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #22
Current rank: #37
Delta: -15
Installs: 8 (prev 18)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Explainer video production guide: scripting, voiceover, visuals, and assembly. Covers script formulas, pacing rules, scene planning, and multi-tool pipelines. Use for: product demos, how-it-works videos, onboarding videos, social explainers. Triggers: explainer video, how to make explainer, product video, demo video, video production, video script, animated explainer, product demo video, tutorial video, onboarding video, walkthrough video, video pipeline]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (31 → 45): prompt-engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/prompt-engineering</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/prompt-engineering</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #31
Current rank: #45
Delta: -14
Installs: 8 (prev 16)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Master prompt engineering for AI models: LLMs, image generators, video models. Techniques: chain-of-thought, few-shot, system prompts, negative prompts. Models: Claude, GPT-4, Gemini, FLUX, Veo, Stable Diffusion prompting. Use for: better AI outputs, consistent results, complex tasks, optimization. Triggers: prompt engineering, how to prompt, better prompts, prompt tips, prompting guide, llm prompting, image prompt, ai prompting, prompt optimization, prompt template, prompt structure, effective prompts, prompt techniques]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (4 → 5): ai-image-generation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/ai-image-generation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/ai-image-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #4
Current rank: #5
Delta: -1
Installs: 46 (prev 100)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Generate AI images with FLUX, Gemini, Grok, Seedream, Reve and 50+ models via inference.sh CLI. Models: FLUX Dev LoRA, FLUX.2 Klein LoRA, Gemini 3 Pro Image, Grok Imagine, Seedream 4.5, Reve, ImagineArt. Capabilities: text-to-image, image-to-image, inpainting, LoRA, image editing, upscaling, text rendering. Use for: AI art, product mockups, concept art, social media graphics, marketing visuals, illustrations. Triggers: flux, image generation, ai image, text to image, stable diffusion, generate image, ai art, midjourney alternative, dall-e alternative, text2img, t2i, image generator, ai picture, create image with ai, generative ai, ai illustration, grok image, gemini image]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (8 → 9): python-sdk]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/python-sdk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/python-sdk</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #8
Current rank: #9
Delta: -1
Installs: 14 (prev 26)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Python SDK for inference.sh - run AI apps, build agents, and integrate with 150+ models. Package: inferencesh (pip install inferencesh). Supports sync/async, streaming, file uploads. Build agents with template or ad-hoc patterns, tool builder API, skills, and human approval. Use for: Python integration, AI apps, agent development, RAG pipelines, automation. Triggers: python sdk, inferencesh, pip install, python api, python client, async inference, python agent, tool builder python, programmatic ai, python integration, sdk python]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (9 → 26): chat-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/chat-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/chat-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #9
Current rank: #26
Delta: -17
Installs: 10 (prev 24)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: name: chat-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (15 → 12): remotion-best-practices]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/remotion-dev/skills/remotion-best-practices</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:remotion-dev/skills/remotion-best-practices</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #15
Current rank: #12
Delta: +3
Installs: 65 (prev 104)
Source: remotion-dev/skills
Description: Best practices for Remotion - Video creation in React]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (18 → 14): app-store-screenshots]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/app-store-screenshots</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/app-store-screenshots</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #18
Current rank: #14
Delta: +4
Installs: 12 (prev 19)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: App Store and Google Play screenshot creation with exact platform specs. Covers iOS/Android dimensions, gallery ordering, device mockups, and preview videos. Use for: app store optimization, ASO, app screenshots, app preview, play store listing. Triggers: app store screenshots, aso, app store optimization, play store screenshots, app preview, app listing, ios screenshots, android screenshots, app store images, app mockup, device mockup, app gallery, store listing]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (34 → 8): text-to-speech]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/text-to-speech</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/text-to-speech</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #34
Current rank: #8
Delta: +26
Installs: 15 (prev 15)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Convert text to natural speech with DIA TTS, Kokoro, Chatterbox, and more via inference.sh CLI. Models: DIA TTS (conversational), Kokoro TTS, Chatterbox, Higgs Audio, VibeVoice (podcasts). Capabilities: text-to-speech, voice cloning, multi-speaker dialogue, podcast generation, expressive speech. Use for: voiceovers, audiobooks, podcasts, accessibility, video narration, IVR, voice assistants. Triggers: text to speech, tts, voice generation, ai voice, speech synthesis, voice over, generate speech, ai narrator, voice cloning, text to audio, elevenlabs alternative, voice ai, ai voiceover, speech generator, natural voice]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (35 → 21): ai-social-media-content]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/ai-social-media-content</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/ai-social-media-content</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #35
Current rank: #21
Delta: +14
Installs: 10 (prev 15)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Create AI-powered social media content for TikTok, Instagram, YouTube, Twitter/X. Generate: images, videos, reels, shorts, thumbnails, captions, hashtags. Tools: FLUX, Veo, Seedance, Wan, Kokoro TTS, Claude for copywriting. Use for: content creators, social media managers, influencers, brands. Triggers: social media content, tiktok, instagram reels, youtube shorts, twitter post, content creator, ai influencer, social content, reels, shorts, viral content, thumbnail generator, caption generator, hashtag generator, ugc content]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (36 → 15): talking-head-production]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/talking-head-production</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/talking-head-production</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #36
Current rank: #15
Delta: +21
Installs: 11 (prev 15)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Talking head video production with AI avatars, lipsync, and voiceover. Covers portrait requirements, audio quality, OmniHuman, PixVerse lipsync, Dia TTS. Use for: spokesperson videos, course content, social media, presentations, demos. Triggers: talking head, avatar video, lipsync, lip sync, ai spokesperson, virtual presenter, ai presenter, omnihuman, talking avatar, video presenter, ai talking head, presenter video, ai face video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (38 → 16): email-design]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/email-design</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/email-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #38
Current rank: #16
Delta: +22
Installs: 11 (prev 15)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Email marketing design with layout patterns, subject line formulas, and deliverability rules. Covers welcome sequences, promotional emails, transactional templates, and mobile optimization. Use for: email marketing, newsletter design, drip campaigns, email templates, transactional emails. Triggers: email design, email template, email marketing, newsletter design, email layout, email campaign, drip campaign, welcome email, promotional email, transactional email, email subject line, email header image, email banner]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (42 → 13): ai-marketing-videos]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/ai-marketing-videos</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/ai-marketing-videos</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #42
Current rank: #13
Delta: +29
Installs: 12 (prev 14)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Create AI marketing videos for ads, promos, product launches, and brand content. Models: Veo, Seedance, Wan, FLUX for visuals, Kokoro for voiceover. Types: product demos, testimonials, explainers, social ads, brand videos. Use for: Facebook ads, YouTube ads, product launches, brand awareness. Triggers: marketing video, ad video, promo video, commercial, brand video, product video, explainer video, ad creative, video ad, facebook ad video, youtube ad, instagram ad, tiktok ad, promotional video, launch video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (43 → 11): video-prompting-guide]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/video-prompting-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/video-prompting-guide</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #43
Current rank: #11
Delta: +32
Installs: 13 (prev 14)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Best practices and techniques for writing effective AI video generation prompts. Covers: Veo, Seedance, Wan, Grok, Kling, Runway, Pika, Sora prompting strategies. Learn: shot types, camera movements, lighting, pacing, style keywords, negative prompts. Use for: improving video quality, getting consistent results, professional video prompts. Triggers: video prompt, how to prompt video, veo prompts, video generation tips, better ai video, video prompt engineering, video prompt guide, video prompt template, ai video tips, video prompt best practices, video prompt examples, cinematography prompts]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (44 → 10): javascript-sdk]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/javascript-sdk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/javascript-sdk</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #44
Current rank: #10
Delta: +34
Installs: 14 (prev 14)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: JavaScript/TypeScript SDK for inference.sh - run AI apps, build agents, integrate 150+ models. Package: @inferencesh/sdk (npm install). Full TypeScript support, streaming, file uploads. Build agents with template or ad-hoc patterns, tool builder API, skills, human approval. Use for: JavaScript integration, TypeScript, Node.js, React, Next.js, frontend apps. Triggers: javascript sdk, typescript sdk, npm install, node.js api, js client, react ai, next.js ai, frontend sdk, @inferencesh/sdk, typescript agent, browser sdk, js integration]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (46 → 32): pitch-deck-visuals]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/pitch-deck-visuals</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/pitch-deck-visuals</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #46
Current rank: #32
Delta: +14
Installs: 9 (prev 13)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Investor pitch deck structure with slide-by-slide framework, visual design rules, and data presentation. Covers the 12-slide framework, chart types, team slides, and common investor turn-offs. Use for: fundraising decks, investor presentations, startup pitch, demo day, grant proposals. Triggers: pitch deck, investor deck, startup pitch, fundraising deck, demo day, pitch presentation, investor presentation, seed deck, series a deck, pitch slides, startup presentation, vc pitch, investor meeting]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (47 → 22): data-visualization]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/data-visualization</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/data-visualization</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #47
Current rank: #22
Delta: +25
Installs: 10 (prev 13)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Data visualization with chart selection, color theory, and annotation best practices. Covers chart types (bar, line, scatter, heatmap), axes rules, and storytelling with data. Use for: charts, graphs, dashboards, reports, presentations, infographics, data stories. Triggers: data visualization, chart, graph, data chart, bar chart, line chart, scatter plot, data viz, visualization, dashboard chart, infographic data, data presentation, chart design, plot, heatmap, pie chart alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (5 → 4): ai-video-generation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-6/skills/ai-video-generation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:inference-sh-6/skills/ai-video-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #5
Current rank: #4
Delta: +1
Installs: 50 (prev 95)
Source: inference-sh-6/skills
Description: Generate AI videos with Google Veo, Seedance, Wan, Grok and 40+ models via inference.sh CLI. Models: Veo 3.1, Veo 3, Seedance 1.5 Pro, Wan 2.5, Grok Imagine Video, OmniHuman, Fabric, HunyuanVideo. Capabilities: text-to-video, image-to-video, lipsync, avatar animation, video upscaling, foley sound. Use for: social media videos, marketing content, explainer videos, product demos, AI avatars. Triggers: video generation, ai video, text to video, image to video, veo, animate image, video from image, ai animation, video generator, generate video, t2v, i2v, ai video maker, create video with ai, runway alternative, pika alternative, sora alternative, kling alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank up (7 → 3): audit-website]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/squirrelscan/skills/audit-website</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topHot:rank:squirrelscan/skills/audit-website</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #7
Current rank: #3
Delta: +4
Installs: 102 (prev 64)
Source: squirrelscan/skills
Description: Audit websites for SEO, performance, security, technical, content, and 15 other issue cateories with 150+ rules using the squirrelscan CLI. Returns LLM-optimized reports with health scores, broken links, meta tag analysis, and actionable recommendations. Use to discover and asses website or webapp issues and health.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] Rank down (1 → 3): find-skills]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/vercel-labs/skills/find-skills</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22T02:42:02.671Z:topTrending:rank:vercel-labs/skills/find-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Trending leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #1
Current rank: #3
Delta: -2
Installs: 6960 (prev 7164)
Source: vercel-labs/skills
Description: Helps users discover and install agent skills when they ask questions like "how do I do X", "find a skill for X", "is there a skill that can...", or express interest in extending capabilities. This skill should be used when the user is looking for functionality that might exist as an installable skill.]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>