<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Skills.sh Feed</title>
        <link>https://skills.sh</link>
        <description>Latest skill data from skills.sh</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Daily] Skills.sh snapshot (2026-02-12)]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:snapshot</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Daily snapshot.
Providers: skills.sh
All Time skills: 27692
Trending skills: 8437
Hot skills: 1732
Top All Time: find-skills (191567)
Top Trending: find-skills (11587)
Top Hot: agent-tools (208)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#37): agent-tools]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inf-sh/skills/agent-tools</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topAllTime:new:inf-sh/skills/agent-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #37
Installs: 6390
Source: inf-sh/skills
Description: Run 150+ AI apps via inference.sh CLI - image generation, video creation, LLMs, search, 3D, Twitter automation. Models: FLUX, Veo, Gemini, Grok, Claude, Seedance, OmniHuman, Tavily, Exa, OpenRouter, and many more. Use when running AI apps, generating images/videos, calling LLMs, web search, or automating Twitter. Triggers: inference.sh, infsh, ai model, run ai, serverless ai, ai api, flux, veo, claude api, image generation, video generation, openrouter, tavily, exa search, twitter api, grok]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#48): content-strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/coreyhaines31/marketingskills/content-strategy</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topAllTime:new:coreyhaines31/marketingskills/content-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #48
Installs: 5732
Source: coreyhaines31/marketingskills
Description: When the user wants to plan a content strategy, decide what content to create, or figure out what topics to cover. Also use when the user mentions "content strategy," "what should I write about," "content ideas," "blog strategy," "topic clusters," or "content planning." For writing individual pieces, see copywriting. For SEO-specific audits, see seo-audit.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#1): agent-tools]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inf-sh/skills/agent-tools</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:inf-sh/skills/agent-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #1
Installs: 208
Source: inf-sh/skills
Description: Run 150+ AI apps via inference.sh CLI - image generation, video creation, LLMs, search, 3D, Twitter automation. Models: FLUX, Veo, Gemini, Grok, Claude, Seedance, OmniHuman, Tavily, Exa, OpenRouter, and many more. Use when running AI apps, generating images/videos, calling LLMs, web search, or automating Twitter. Triggers: inference.sh, infsh, ai model, run ai, serverless ai, ai api, flux, veo, claude api, image generation, video generation, openrouter, tavily, exa search, twitter api, grok]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#10): youtube-thumbnail-design]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/youtube-thumbnail-design</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/youtube-thumbnail-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #10
Installs: 28
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: YouTube thumbnail design with specific dimensions, contrast rules, and mobile preview optimization. Covers safe zones, text placement, face expression psychology, and A/B testing. Use for: YouTube thumbnails, video cover images, click-through optimization. Triggers: youtube thumbnail, thumbnail design, video thumbnail, click through rate, ctr optimization, youtube cover, video cover image, thumbnail maker, thumbnail tips, youtube design, video preview image]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#11): product-hunt-launch]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/product-hunt-launch</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/product-hunt-launch</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #11
Installs: 27
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Product Hunt launch optimization with specific specs, timing, and gallery strategy. Covers taglines, gallery images, maker comments, and launch day tactics. Use for: product launches, startup launches, side project launches, Product Hunt optimization. Triggers: product hunt, ph launch, product hunt launch, launch strategy, product launch, startup launch, product hunt tips, product hunt gallery, ph optimization, launch day, product hunt maker]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#12): press-release-writing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/press-release-writing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/press-release-writing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #12
Installs: 27
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Press release writing in AP style with inverted pyramid structure. Covers formatting, datelines, quotes, boilerplates, and fact-checking. Use for: product launches, funding announcements, partnerships, company news, events. Triggers: press release, pr writing, media release, news release, announcement, product launch announcement, funding announcement, company news, media advisory, ap style, press statement, news wire]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#13): social-media-carousel]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/social-media-carousel</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/social-media-carousel</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #13
Installs: 26
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Multi-slide carousel design for Instagram, LinkedIn, and Twitter/X with layout rules and hooks. Covers slide structure, text hierarchy, swipe psychology, and platform-specific specs. Use for: carousel posts, Instagram carousels, LinkedIn carousels, slide posts, educational content. Triggers: carousel, instagram carousel, linkedin carousel, slide post, carousel design, swipe post, multi-image post, carousel template, educational carousel, carousel content, instagram slides, linkedin slides]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#14): flux-image]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/flux-image</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/flux-image</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #14
Installs: 26
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Generate images with FLUX models (Black Forest Labs) via inference.sh CLI. Models: FLUX Dev LoRA, FLUX.2 Klein LoRA with custom style adaptation. Capabilities: text-to-image, image-to-image, LoRA fine-tuning, custom styles. Triggers: flux, flux.2, flux dev, flux schnell, flux pro, black forest labs, flux image, flux ai, flux model, flux lora]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#15): llm-models]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/llm-models</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/llm-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #15
Installs: 25
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Access Claude, Gemini, Kimi, GLM and 100+ LLMs via inference.sh CLI using OpenRouter. Models: Claude Opus 4.5, Claude Sonnet 4.5, Claude Haiku 4.5, Gemini 3 Pro, Kimi K2, GLM-4.6, Intellect 3. One API for all models with automatic fallback and cost optimization. Use for: AI assistants, code generation, reasoning, agents, chat, content generation. Triggers: claude api, openrouter, llm api, claude sonnet, claude opus, gemini api, kimi, language model, gpt alternative, anthropic api, ai model api, llm access, chat api, claude alternative, openai alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#16): email-design]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/email-design</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/email-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #16
Installs: 25
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Email marketing design with layout patterns, subject line formulas, and deliverability rules. Covers welcome sequences, promotional emails, transactional templates, and mobile optimization. Use for: email marketing, newsletter design, drip campaigns, email templates, transactional emails. Triggers: email design, email template, email marketing, newsletter design, email layout, email campaign, drip campaign, welcome email, promotional email, transactional email, email subject line, email header image, email banner]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#17): ai-avatar-video]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-avatar-video</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-avatar-video</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #17
Installs: 25
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Create AI avatar and talking head videos with OmniHuman, Fabric, PixVerse via inference.sh CLI. Models: OmniHuman 1.5, OmniHuman 1.0, Fabric 1.0, PixVerse Lipsync. Capabilities: audio-driven avatars, lipsync videos, talking head generation, virtual presenters. Use for: AI presenters, explainer videos, virtual influencers, dubbing, marketing videos. Triggers: ai avatar, talking head, lipsync, avatar video, virtual presenter, ai spokesperson, audio driven video, heygen alternative, synthesia alternative, talking avatar, lip sync, video avatar, ai presenter, digital human]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#18): customer-persona]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/customer-persona</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/customer-persona</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #18
Installs: 25
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Research-backed customer persona creation with market data and avatar generation. Covers demographics, psychographics, jobs-to-be-done, journey mapping, and anti-personas. Use for: marketing strategy, product development, UX research, sales enablement, content strategy. Triggers: customer persona, buyer persona, user persona, target audience, ideal customer, customer profile, audience research, user research, icp, ideal customer profile, target market, customer avatar, audience persona]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#19): case-study-writing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/case-study-writing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/case-study-writing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #19
Installs: 24
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: B2B case study writing with STAR framework, data visualization, and research. Covers structure, customer quotes, metrics presentation, and distribution formats. Use for: customer success stories, portfolio pieces, sales enablement, marketing content. Triggers: case study, customer story, success story, b2b case study, client testimonial, customer case study, portfolio case study, use case, customer win, results story]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#2): agent-browser]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inf-sh/skills/agent-browser</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:inf-sh/skills/agent-browser</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #2
Installs: 94
Source: inf-sh/skills
Description: Browser automation for AI agents via inference.sh. Navigate web pages, interact with elements using @e refs, take screenshots, record video. Capabilities: web scraping, form filling, clicking, typing, drag-drop, file upload, JavaScript execution. Use for: web automation, data extraction, testing, agent browsing, research. Triggers: browser, web automation, scrape, navigate, click, fill form, screenshot, browse web, playwright, headless browser, web agent, surf internet, record video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#20): dialogue-audio]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/dialogue-audio</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/dialogue-audio</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #20
Installs: 24
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Multi-speaker dialogue audio creation with Dia TTS. Covers speaker tags, emotion control, pacing, conversation flow, and post-production. Use for: podcasts, audiobooks, explainers, character dialogue, conversational content. Triggers: dialogue audio, multi speaker, conversation audio, dia tts, two speakers, podcast audio, character voices, voice acting, dialogue generation, conversation tts, multi voice, speaker tags, dialogue recording]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#21): character-design-sheet]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/character-design-sheet</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/character-design-sheet</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #21
Installs: 24
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Character consistency across AI-generated images with reference sheets and LoRA techniques. Covers turnaround views, expression sheets, color palettes, and style consistency tricks. Use for: character design, game art, illustration, animation, comics, visual novels. Triggers: character design, character sheet, character consistency, character reference, turnaround sheet, expression sheet, character art, consistent character, character concept, reference sheet, character creation, oc design, character bible]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#22): ai-voice-cloning]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-voice-cloning</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-voice-cloning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #22
Installs: 23
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: AI voice generation, text-to-speech, and voice synthesis via inference.sh CLI. Models: Kokoro TTS, DIA, Chatterbox, Higgs, VibeVoice for natural speech. Capabilities: multiple voices, emotions, accents, long-form narration, conversation. Use for: voiceovers, audiobooks, podcasts, video narration, accessibility. Triggers: voice cloning, tts, text to speech, ai voice, voice generation, voice synthesis, voice over, narration, speech synthesis, ai narrator, elevenlabs alternative, natural voice, realistic speech, voice ai]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#23): technical-blog-writing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/technical-blog-writing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/technical-blog-writing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #23
Installs: 23
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Technical blog post writing with structure, code examples, and developer audience conventions. Covers post types, code formatting, explanation depth, and developer-specific engagement patterns. Use for: engineering blogs, dev tutorials, technical writing, developer content, documentation posts. Triggers: technical blog, dev blog, engineering blog, technical writing, developer tutorial, tech post, code tutorial, programming blog, developer content, technical article, engineering post, coding tutorial, technical content]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#24): storyboard-creation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/storyboard-creation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/storyboard-creation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #24
Installs: 22
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Film and video storyboarding with shot vocabulary, continuity rules, and panel layout. Covers shot types, camera angles, movement, 180-degree rule, and annotation format. Use for: video planning, film pre-production, ad storyboards, music video planning, animation. Triggers: storyboard, storyboarding, shot list, film planning, video planning, pre production, shot composition, camera angles, scene planning, visual script, animatic, storyboard panels, video storyboard]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#25): competitor-teardown]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/competitor-teardown</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/competitor-teardown</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #25
Installs: 22
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Structured competitive analysis with feature matrices, SWOT, positioning maps, and UX review. Covers research frameworks, pricing comparison, review mining, and visual deliverables. Use for: market research, competitive intelligence, investor decks, product strategy, sales enablement. Triggers: competitor analysis, competitive analysis, competitor teardown, market research, competitive intelligence, swot analysis, competitor comparison, market landscape, competitor review, competitive landscape, feature comparison, market positioning]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#26): python-sdk]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inf-sh/skills/python-sdk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:inf-sh/skills/python-sdk</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #26
Installs: 22
Source: inf-sh/skills
Description: Python SDK for inference.sh - run AI apps, build agents, and integrate with 150+ models. Package: inferencesh (pip install inferencesh). Supports sync/async, streaming, file uploads. Build agents with template or ad-hoc patterns, tool builder API, skills, and human approval. Use for: Python integration, AI apps, agent development, RAG pipelines, automation. Triggers: python sdk, inferencesh, pip install, python api, python client, async inference, python agent, tool builder python, programmatic ai, python integration, sdk python]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#27): data-visualization]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/data-visualization</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/data-visualization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #27
Installs: 21
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Data visualization with chart selection, color theory, and annotation best practices. Covers chart types (bar, line, scatter, heatmap), axes rules, and storytelling with data. Use for: charts, graphs, dashboards, reports, presentations, infographics, data stories. Triggers: data visualization, chart, graph, data chart, bar chart, line chart, scatter plot, data viz, visualization, dashboard chart, infographic data, data presentation, chart design, plot, heatmap, pie chart alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#28): ai-social-media-content]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-social-media-content</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-social-media-content</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #28
Installs: 21
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Create AI-powered social media content for TikTok, Instagram, YouTube, Twitter/X. Generate: images, videos, reels, shorts, thumbnails, captions, hashtags. Tools: FLUX, Veo, Seedance, Wan, Kokoro TTS, Claude for copywriting. Use for: content creators, social media managers, influencers, brands. Triggers: social media content, tiktok, instagram reels, youtube shorts, twitter post, content creator, ai influencer, social content, reels, shorts, viral content, thumbnail generator, caption generator, hashtag generator, ugc content]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#29): product-changelog]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/product-changelog</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/product-changelog</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #29
Installs: 21
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Product changelog and release notes that users actually read. Covers categorization, user-facing language, visuals, and distribution. Use for: release notes, changelogs, product updates, feature announcements, versioning. Triggers: changelog, release notes, product update, version notes, what's new, feature announcement, product changelog, update log, release announcement, version release, product release, ship notes]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#3): content-strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/coreyhaines31/marketingskills/content-strategy</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:coreyhaines31/marketingskills/content-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #3
Installs: 84
Source: coreyhaines31/marketingskills
Description: When the user wants to plan a content strategy, decide what content to create, or figure out what topics to cover. Also use when the user mentions "content strategy," "what should I write about," "content ideas," "blog strategy," "topic clusters," or "content planning." For writing individual pieces, see copywriting. For SEO-specific audits, see seo-audit.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#30): seo-content-brief]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/seo-content-brief</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/seo-content-brief</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #30
Installs: 20
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: SEO content brief creation with keyword research, search intent analysis, and content structure. Covers SERP analysis, heading hierarchy, word count targets, and internal linking strategy. Use for: content briefs, SEO writing, blog strategy, content planning, keyword targeting. Triggers: seo content brief, content brief, seo brief, keyword research, search intent, content strategy, blog brief, seo writing, content planning, keyword targeting, serp analysis, content outline, seo article, blog seo]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#31): ai-podcast-creation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-podcast-creation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-podcast-creation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #31
Installs: 19
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Create AI-powered podcasts with text-to-speech, music, and audio editing. Tools: Kokoro TTS, DIA TTS, Chatterbox, AI music generation, media merger. Capabilities: multi-voice conversations, background music, intro/outro, full episodes. Use for: podcast production, audiobooks, voice content, audio newsletters. Triggers: podcast, ai podcast, text to speech podcast, audio content, voice over, ai audiobook, multi voice, conversation ai, notebooklm alternative, audio generation, podcast automation, ai narrator, voice content, audio newsletter, podcast maker]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#32): twitter-thread-creation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/twitter-thread-creation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/twitter-thread-creation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #32
Installs: 19
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Twitter/X thread writing with hook tweets, thread structure, and engagement optimization. Covers tweet formatting, character limits, media attachments, and posting strategies. Use for: Twitter threads, X posts, tweet storms, Twitter content, social media writing. Triggers: twitter thread, tweet thread, x thread, twitter post, tweet writing, thread creation, tweet storm, twitter content, x post, twitter writing, twitter hook, tweet formatting, thread structure]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#33): speech-to-text]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/speech-to-text</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/speech-to-text</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #33
Installs: 19
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Transcribe audio to text with Whisper models via inference.sh CLI. Models: Fast Whisper Large V3, Whisper V3 Large. Capabilities: transcription, translation, multi-language, timestamps. Use for: meeting transcription, subtitles, podcast transcripts, voice notes. Triggers: speech to text, transcription, whisper, audio to text, transcribe audio, voice to text, stt, automatic transcription, subtitles generation, transcribe meeting, audio transcription, whisper ai]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#35): ai-content-pipeline]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-content-pipeline</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-content-pipeline</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #35
Installs: 18
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Build multi-step AI content creation pipelines combining image, video, audio, and text. Workflow examples: generate image -> animate -> add voiceover -> merge with music. Tools: FLUX, Veo, Kokoro TTS, OmniHuman, media merger, upscaling. Use for: YouTube videos, social media content, marketing materials, automated content. Triggers: content pipeline, ai workflow, content creation, multi-step ai, content automation, ai video workflow, generate and edit, ai content factory, automated content creation, ai production pipeline, media pipeline, content at scale]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#36): talking-head-production]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/talking-head-production</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/talking-head-production</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #36
Installs: 18
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Talking head video production with AI avatars, lipsync, and voiceover. Covers portrait requirements, audio quality, OmniHuman, PixVerse lipsync, Dia TTS. Use for: spokesperson videos, course content, social media, presentations, demos. Triggers: talking head, avatar video, lipsync, lip sync, ai spokesperson, virtual presenter, ai presenter, omnihuman, talking avatar, video presenter, ai talking head, presenter video, ai face video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#37): ai-product-photography]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-product-photography</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-product-photography</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #37
Installs: 17
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Generate professional AI product photography and commercial images. Models: FLUX, Imagen 3, Grok, Seedream for product shots, lifestyle images, mockups. Capabilities: studio lighting, lifestyle scenes, packaging, e-commerce photos. Use for: e-commerce, Amazon listings, Shopify, marketing, advertising, mockups. Triggers: product photography, product shot, commercial photography, e-commerce images, amazon product photo, shopify images, product mockup, studio product shot, lifestyle product image, advertising photo, packshot, product render, product image ai]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#38): ai-marketing-videos]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-marketing-videos</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-marketing-videos</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #38
Installs: 17
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Create AI marketing videos for ads, promos, product launches, and brand content. Models: Veo, Seedance, Wan, FLUX for visuals, Kokoro for voiceover. Types: product demos, testimonials, explainers, social ads, brand videos. Use for: Facebook ads, YouTube ads, product launches, brand awareness. Triggers: marketing video, ad video, promo video, commercial, brand video, product video, explainer video, ad creative, video ad, facebook ad video, youtube ad, instagram ad, tiktok ad, promotional video, launch video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#39): video-prompting-guide]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/video-prompting-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/video-prompting-guide</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #39
Installs: 17
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Best practices and techniques for writing effective AI video generation prompts. Covers: Veo, Seedance, Wan, Grok, Kling, Runway, Pika, Sora prompting strategies. Learn: shot types, camera movements, lighting, pacing, style keywords, negative prompts. Use for: improving video quality, getting consistent results, professional video prompts. Triggers: video prompt, how to prompt video, veo prompts, video generation tips, better ai video, video prompt engineering, video prompt guide, video prompt template, ai video tips, video prompt best practices, video prompt examples, cinematography prompts]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#4): ai-video-generation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-video-generation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-video-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #4
Installs: 59
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Generate AI videos with Google Veo, Seedance, Wan, Grok and 40+ models via inference.sh CLI. Models: Veo 3.1, Veo 3, Seedance 1.5 Pro, Wan 2.5, Grok Imagine Video, OmniHuman, Fabric, HunyuanVideo. Capabilities: text-to-video, image-to-video, lipsync, avatar animation, video upscaling, foley sound. Use for: social media videos, marketing content, explainer videos, product demos, AI avatars. Triggers: video generation, ai video, text to video, image to video, veo, animate image, video from image, ai animation, video generator, generate video, t2v, i2v, ai video maker, create video with ai, runway alternative, pika alternative, sora alternative, kling alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#40): explainer-video-guide]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/explainer-video-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/explainer-video-guide</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #40
Installs: 17
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Explainer video production guide: scripting, voiceover, visuals, and assembly. Covers script formulas, pacing rules, scene planning, and multi-tool pipelines. Use for: product demos, how-it-works videos, onboarding videos, social explainers. Triggers: explainer video, how to make explainer, product video, demo video, video production, video script, animated explainer, product demo video, tutorial video, onboarding video, walkthrough video, video pipeline]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#41): ai-automation-workflows]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-automation-workflows</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-automation-workflows</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #41
Installs: 17
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Build automated AI workflows combining multiple models and services. Patterns: batch processing, scheduled tasks, event-driven pipelines, agent loops. Tools: inference.sh CLI, bash scripting, Python SDK, webhook integration. Use for: content automation, data processing, monitoring, scheduled generation. Triggers: ai automation, workflow automation, batch processing, ai pipeline, automated content, scheduled ai, ai cron, ai batch job, automated generation, ai workflow, content at scale, automation script, ai orchestration]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#42): video-ad-specs]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/video-ad-specs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/video-ad-specs</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #42
Installs: 17
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Video ad creation with exact platform-specific specs for TikTok, Instagram, YouTube, Facebook, LinkedIn. Covers dimensions, duration limits, AIDA framework, and caption requirements. Use for: video ads, social media ads, paid media creative, video marketing, ad production. Triggers: video ad, social media ad, tiktok ad, instagram ad, youtube ad, facebook ad, linkedin ad, video creative, ad specs, paid media, video marketing, ad production, reels ad, stories ad, pre roll, bumper ad]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#43): book-cover-design]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/book-cover-design</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/book-cover-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #43
Installs: 16
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Book cover design with genre-specific conventions, typography rules, and AI image generation. Covers fiction and non-fiction genres, sizing, thumbnail testing, and iteration workflows. Use for: self-publishing, ebook covers, print covers, audiobook covers, cover mockups. Triggers: book cover, cover design, ebook cover, book art, novel cover, self publishing cover, kindle cover, audiobook cover, book jacket, cover illustration, fiction cover, nonfiction cover]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#44): pitch-deck-visuals]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/pitch-deck-visuals</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/pitch-deck-visuals</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #44
Installs: 16
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Investor pitch deck structure with slide-by-slide framework, visual design rules, and data presentation. Covers the 12-slide framework, chart types, team slides, and common investor turn-offs. Use for: fundraising decks, investor presentations, startup pitch, demo day, grant proposals. Triggers: pitch deck, investor deck, startup pitch, fundraising deck, demo day, pitch presentation, investor presentation, seed deck, series a deck, pitch slides, startup presentation, vc pitch, investor meeting]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#45): ai-music-generation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-music-generation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-music-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #45
Installs: 16
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Generate AI music and songs with Diffrythm, Tencent Song Generation via inference.sh CLI. Models: Diffrythm (fast song generation), Tencent Song Generation (full songs with vocals). Capabilities: text-to-music, song generation, instrumental, lyrics to song, soundtrack creation. Use for: background music, social media content, game soundtracks, podcasts, royalty-free music. Triggers: music generation, ai music, generate song, ai composer, text to music, song generator, create music with ai, suno alternative, udio alternative, ai song, ai soundtrack, generate soundtrack, ai jingle, music ai, beat generator]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#46): app-store-screenshots]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/app-store-screenshots</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/app-store-screenshots</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #46
Installs: 16
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: App Store and Google Play screenshot creation with exact platform specs. Covers iOS/Android dimensions, gallery ordering, device mockups, and preview videos. Use for: app store optimization, ASO, app screenshots, app preview, play store listing. Triggers: app store screenshots, aso, app store optimization, play store screenshots, app preview, app listing, ios screenshots, android screenshots, app store images, app mockup, device mockup, app gallery, store listing]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#47): linkedin-content]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/linkedin-content</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/linkedin-content</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #47
Installs: 16
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: LinkedIn post writing with hook formulas, formatting rules, and engagement patterns. Covers post types, algorithm signals, character limits, and content pillars. Use for: LinkedIn posts, professional content, thought leadership, B2B content, personal branding. Triggers: linkedin post, linkedin content, linkedin writing, linkedin strategy, linkedin engagement, linkedin algorithm, linkedin hook, linkedin formatting, thought leadership, professional content, b2b content, linkedin growth]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#48): prompt-engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/prompt-engineering</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/prompt-engineering</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #48
Installs: 16
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Master prompt engineering for AI models: LLMs, image generators, video models. Techniques: chain-of-thought, few-shot, system prompts, negative prompts. Models: Claude, GPT-4, Gemini, FLUX, Veo, Stable Diffusion prompting. Use for: better AI outputs, consistent results, complex tasks, optimization. Triggers: prompt engineering, how to prompt, better prompts, prompt tips, prompting guide, llm prompting, image prompt, ai prompting, prompt optimization, prompt template, prompt structure, effective prompts, prompt techniques]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#49): text-to-speech]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/text-to-speech</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/text-to-speech</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #49
Installs: 15
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Convert text to natural speech with DIA TTS, Kokoro, Chatterbox, and more via inference.sh CLI. Models: DIA TTS (conversational), Kokoro TTS, Chatterbox, Higgs Audio, VibeVoice (podcasts). Capabilities: text-to-speech, voice cloning, multi-speaker dialogue, podcast generation, expressive speech. Use for: voiceovers, audiobooks, podcasts, accessibility, video narration, IVR, voice assistants. Triggers: text to speech, tts, voice generation, ai voice, speech synthesis, voice over, generate speech, ai narrator, voice cloning, text to audio, elevenlabs alternative, voice ai, ai voiceover, speech generator, natural voice]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#5): product-marketing-context]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/coreyhaines31/marketingskills/product-marketing-context</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:coreyhaines31/marketingskills/product-marketing-context</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #5
Installs: 65
Source: coreyhaines31/marketingskills
Description: When the user wants to create or update their product marketing context document. Also use when the user mentions 'product context,' 'marketing context,' 'set up context,' 'positioning,' or wants to avoid repeating foundational information across marketing tasks. Creates `.claude/product-marketing-context.md` that other marketing skills reference.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#50): google-veo]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/google-veo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/google-veo</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #50
Installs: 14
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Generate videos with Google Veo models via inference.sh CLI. Models: Veo 3.1, Veo 3.1 Fast, Veo 3, Veo 3 Fast, Veo 2. Capabilities: text-to-video, cinematic output, high quality video generation. Triggers: veo, google veo, veo 3, veo 2, veo 3.1, vertex ai video, google video generation, google video ai, veo model, veo video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#6): find-skills]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/vercel-labs/add-skill/find-skills</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:vercel-labs/add-skill/find-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #6
Installs: 55
Source: vercel-labs/add-skill
Description: Helps users discover and install agent skills when they ask questions like "how do I do X", "find a skill for X", "is there a skill that can...", or express interest in extending capabilities. This skill should be used when the user is looking for functionality that might exist as an installable skill.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#7): ai-image-generation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/ai-image-generation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/ai-image-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #7
Installs: 43
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Generate AI images with FLUX, Gemini, Grok, Seedream, Reve and 50+ models via inference.sh CLI. Models: FLUX Dev LoRA, FLUX.2 Klein LoRA, Gemini 3 Pro Image, Grok Imagine, Seedream 4.5, Reve, ImagineArt. Capabilities: text-to-image, image-to-image, inpainting, LoRA, image editing, upscaling, text rendering. Use for: AI art, product mockups, concept art, social media graphics, marketing visuals, illustrations. Triggers: flux, image generation, ai image, text to image, stable diffusion, generate image, ai art, midjourney alternative, dall-e alternative, text2img, t2i, image generator, ai picture, create image with ai, generative ai, ai illustration, grok image, gemini image]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#8): twitter-automation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/skill-zero/s/twitter-automation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12T03:14:43.630Z:topHot:new:skill-zero/s/twitter-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #8
Installs: 32
Source: skill-zero/s
Description: Automate Twitter/X with posting, engagement, and user management via inference.sh CLI. Apps: x/post-tweet, x/post-create (with media), x/post-like, x/post-retweet, x/dm-send, x/user-follow. Capabilities: post tweets, schedule content, like posts, retweet, send DMs, follow users, get profiles. Use for: social media automation, content scheduling, engagement bots, audience growth, X API. Triggers: twitter api, x api, tweet automation, post to twitter, twitter bot, social media automation, x automation, tweet scheduler, twitter integration, post tweet, twitter post, x post, send tweet]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>