<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Skills.sh Feed</title>
        <link>https://skills.sh</link>
        <description>Latest skill data from skills.sh</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Daily] Skills.sh snapshot (2026-02-20)]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:snapshot</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Daily snapshot.
Providers: skills.sh
All Time skills: 31015
Trending skills: 12119
Hot skills: 1524
Top All Time: find-skills (277307)
Top Trending: agent-tools (12103)
Top Hot: azure-rbac (627)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#26): azure-kusto]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-kusto</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-kusto</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #26
Installs: 12305
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Query and analyze data in Azure Data Explorer (Kusto/ADX) using KQL for log analytics, telemetry, and time series analysis.
USE FOR: KQL queries, Kusto database queries, Azure Data Explorer, ADX clusters, log analytics, time series data, IoT telemetry, anomaly detection
DO NOT USE FOR: SQL databases (use azure-postgres), NoSQL queries (use azure-storage), Elasticsearch, AWS analytics tools]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#27): azure-storage]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-storage</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-storage</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #27
Installs: 12304
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Azure Storage Services including Blob Storage, File Shares, Queue Storage, Table Storage, and Data Lake. Provides object storage, SMB file shares, async messaging, NoSQL key-value, and big data analytics capabilities. Includes access tiers (hot, cool, archive) and lifecycle management.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#28): azure-diagnostics]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-diagnostics</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-diagnostics</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #28
Installs: 12304
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Debug and troubleshoot production issues on Azure. Covers Container Apps diagnostics, log analysis with KQL, health checks, and common issue resolution for image pulls, cold starts, and health probes.
USE FOR: debug production issues, troubleshoot container apps, analyze logs with KQL, fix image pull failures, resolve cold start issues, investigate health probe failures, check resource health, view application logs, find root cause of errors
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying applications (use azure-deploy), creating new resources (use azure-prepare), setting up monitoring (use azure-observability), cost optimization (use azure-cost-optimization)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#29): azure-ai]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-ai</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #29
Installs: 12302
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Use for Azure AI: Search, Speech, OpenAI, Document Intelligence. Helps with search, vector/hybrid search, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, transcription, OCR. USE FOR: AI Search, query search, vector search, hybrid search, semantic search, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, transcribe, OCR, convert text to speech. DO NOT USE FOR: Function apps/Functions (use azure-functions), databases (azure-postgres/azure-kusto), general Azure resources.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#30): azure-cost-optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-cost-optimization</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-cost-optimization</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #30
Installs: 12302
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Identify and quantify cost savings across Azure subscriptions by analyzing actual costs,
utilization metrics, and generating actionable optimization recommendations. USE FOR:
optimize Azure costs, reduce Azure spending, reduce Azure expenses, analyze Azure costs,
find cost savings, generate cost optimization report, find orphaned resources, rightsize VMs,
cost analysis, reduce waste, Azure spending analysis, find unused resources, optimize Redis
costs. DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), general Azure diagnostics
(use azure-diagnostics), security issues (use azure-security)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#31): azure-resource-visualizer]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-visualizer</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-visualizer</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #31
Installs: 12301
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Analyze Azure resource groups and generate detailed Mermaid architecture diagrams showing the relationships between individual resources.
USE FOR: create architecture diagram, visualize Azure resources, show resource relationships, generate Mermaid diagram, analyze resource group, diagram my resources, architecture visualization, resource topology, map Azure infrastructure
DO NOT USE FOR: creating/modifying resources (use azure-deploy), security scanning (use azure-security), performance troubleshooting (use azure-diagnostics), code generation (use relevant service skill)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#32): entra-app-registration]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/entra-app-registration</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/entra-app-registration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #32
Installs: 12300
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Guides Microsoft Entra ID app registration, OAuth 2.0 authentication, and MSAL integration.
USE FOR: create app registration, register Azure AD app, configure OAuth, set up authentication, add API permissions, generate service principal, MSAL example, console app auth, Entra ID setup, Azure AD authentication.
DO NOT USE FOR: Azure RBAC or role assignments (use azure-rbac), Key Vault secrets (use azure-keyvault-expiration-audit), Azure resource security (use azure-security).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#33): azure-validate]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-validate</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-validate</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #33
Installs: 12298
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Pre-deployment validation checkpoint. Run deep checks to ensure your application is ready for Azure deployment. Validates configuration, infrastructure, permissions, and prerequisites.
USE FOR: validate my app, check deployment readiness, run preflight checks, verify configuration, check if ready to deploy, validate azure.yaml, validate Bicep, test before deploying, troubleshoot deployment errors.
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or building apps (use azure-prepare), executing deployments (use azure-deploy).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#34): azure-deploy]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-deploy</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-deploy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #34
Installs: 12298
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Execute deployment to Azure. Final step after preparation and validation. Runs azd up, azd deploy, or infrastructure provisioning commands.
USE FOR: run azd up, run azd deploy, execute deployment, provision infrastructure, push to production, go live, ship it, deploy web app, deploy container app, deploy static site, deploy Azure Functions, bicep deploy, terraform apply.
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or building apps (use azure-prepare), validating before deploy (use azure-validate).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#35): azure-postgres]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-postgres</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-postgres</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #35
Installs: 12298
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Create new Azure Database for PostgreSQL Flexible Server instances and configure passwordless authentication with Microsoft Entra ID. Set up developer access, managed identities for apps, group-based permissions, and migrate from password-based to Entra ID authentication. Trigger phrases include "passwordless for postgres", "entra id postgres", "azure ad postgres authentication", "postgres managed identity", "migrate postgres to passwordless".]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#36): microsoft-foundry]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/microsoft-foundry</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/microsoft-foundry</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #36
Installs: 12298
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Use this skill to work with Microsoft Foundry (Azure AI Foundry): deploy AI models from catalog, build RAG applications with knowledge indexes, create and evaluate AI agents, manage RBAC permissions and role assignments, manage quotas and capacity, create Foundry resources.
USE FOR: Microsoft Foundry, AI Foundry, deploy model, model catalog, RAG, knowledge index, create agent, evaluate agent, agent monitoring, create Foundry project, new Foundry project, set up Foundry, onboard to Foundry, provision Foundry infrastructure, create Foundry resource, create AI Services, multi-service resource, AIServices kind, register resource provider, enable Cognitive Services, setup AI Services account, create resource group for Foundry, RBAC, role assignment, managed identity, service principal, permissions, quota, capacity, TPM, deployment failure, QuotaExceeded.
DO NOT USE FOR: Azure Functions (use azure-functions), App Service (use azure-create-app), generic Azure resource creation (use azure-create-app).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#37): azure-prepare]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-prepare</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-prepare</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #37
Installs: 12298
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Default entry point for Azure application development. Invoke this skill for ANY application work related to Azure: creating apps, building features, adding components, updating code, migrating, or modernizing. Analyzes your project and prepares it for Azure deployment by generating infrastructure code (Bicep/Terraform), azure.yaml configuration, and Dockerfiles.
USE FOR: create an app, build a web app, create API, create frontend, create backend, add a feature, build a service, make an application, develop a project, migrate my app, modernize my code, update my application, add database, add authentication, add caching, deploy to Azure, host on Azure, Azure with Terraform (defaults to azd+Terraform), Azure with azd, generate azure.yaml, generate Bicep or Terraform, prepare Azure Functions.
DO NOT USE FOR: only validating an already-prepared app (use azure-validate), only running azd up/deploy (use azure-deploy), pure Terraform without azd (prefer azd+Terraform).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#38): appinsights-instrumentation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/appinsights-instrumentation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/appinsights-instrumentation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #38
Installs: 12297
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Guidance for instrumenting webapps with Azure Application Insights. Provides telemetry patterns, SDK setup, and configuration references.
USE FOR: how to instrument app, App Insights SDK, telemetry patterns, what is App Insights, Application Insights guidance, instrumentation examples, APM best practices.
DO NOT USE FOR: adding App Insights to my app (use azure-prepare), add telemetry to my project (use azure-prepare), add monitoring (use azure-prepare). This skill provides guidance—azure-prepare orchestrates component changes.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#39): azure-compliance]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-compliance</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-compliance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #39
Installs: 12297
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Comprehensive Azure compliance and security auditing capabilities including best practices assessment,
Key Vault expiration monitoring, and resource configuration validation.
USE FOR: compliance scan, security audit, azqr, Azure best practices, Key Vault expiration check,
compliance assessment, resource review, configuration validation, expired certificates, expiring secrets,
orphaned resources, policy compliance, security posture evaluation.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), cost analysis alone (use azure-cost-optimization),
active security hardening (use azure-security-hardening), general Azure Advisor queries (use azure-observability).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#40): azure-aigateway]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-aigateway</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-aigateway</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #40
Installs: 12297
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Configure Azure API Management (APIM) as AI Gateway to secure, observe, control AI models, MCP servers, agents. Helps with rate limiting, semantic caching, content safety, load balancing.
USE FOR: AI Gateway, APIM, setup gateway, configure gateway, add gateway, model gateway, MCP server, rate limit, token limit, semantic cache, content safety, load balance, OpenAPI import, convert API to MCP.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploy models (use microsoft-foundry), Azure Functions (use azure-functions), databases (use azure-postgres).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#42): azure-rbac]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-rbac</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-rbac</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #42
Installs: 12292
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Helps users find the right Azure RBAC role for an identity with least privilege access, then generate CLI commands and Bicep code to assign it.
USE FOR: "what role should I assign", "least privilege role", "RBAC role for", "role to read blobs", "role for managed identity", "custom role definition", "assign role to identity".
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or configuring managed identities, or general Azure security hardening; those are out of scope for this role-selection skill.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#43): azure-resource-lookup]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-lookup</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-lookup</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #43
Installs: 12292
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: List, find, and show Azure resources. Answers "list my VMs", "show my storage accounts", "list websites",
"find container apps", "what resources do I have", and similar queries for any Azure resource type.
USE FOR: list resources, list virtual machines, list VMs, list storage accounts, list websites, list web apps,
list container apps, show resources, find resources, what resources do I have, list resources in resource group,
list resources in subscription, find resources by tag, find orphaned resources, resource inventory,
count resources by type, cross-subscription resource query, Azure Resource Graph, resource discovery,
list container registries, list SQL servers, list Key Vaults, show resource groups, list app services,
find resources across subscriptions, find unattached disks, tag analysis.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), creating or modifying resources,
cost optimization (use azure-cost-optimization), writing application code, non-Azure clouds.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#44): agent-tools]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-tools</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #44
Installs: 12257
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Run 150+ AI apps via inference.sh CLI - image generation, video creation, LLMs, search, 3D, Twitter automation. Models: FLUX, Veo, Gemini, Grok, Claude, Seedance, OmniHuman, Tavily, Exa, OpenRouter, and many more. Use when running AI apps, generating images/videos, calling LLMs, web search, or automating Twitter. Triggers: inference.sh, infsh, ai model, run ai, serverless ai, ai api, flux, veo, claude api, image generation, video generation, openrouter, tavily, exa search, twitter api, grok]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#20): remotion-render]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/remotion-render</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/remotion-render</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #20
Installs: 358
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Render videos from React/Remotion component code via inference.sh. Pass TSX code, get MP4. Supports all Remotion APIs: useCurrentFrame, useVideoConfig, spring, interpolate, AbsoluteFill, Sequence. Configurable resolution, FPS, duration, codec. Use for: programmatic video generation, animated graphics, motion design, data-driven videos, React animations to video. Triggers: remotion, render video from code, tsx to video, react video, programmatic video, remotion render, code to video, animated video, motion graphics code, react animation video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#21): mcp-apps-builder]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/mcp-use/mcp-use/mcp-apps-builder</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:mcp-use/mcp-use/mcp-apps-builder</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #21
Installs: 172
Source: mcp-use/mcp-use
Description: **MANDATORY for ALL MCP server work** - mcp-use framework best practices and patterns.

**READ THIS FIRST** before any MCP server work, including:
- Creating new MCP servers
- Modifying existing MCP servers (adding/updating tools, resources, prompts, widgets)
- Debugging MCP server issues or errors
- Reviewing MCP server code for quality, security, or performance
- Answering questions about MCP development or mcp-use patterns
- Making ANY changes to server.tool(), server.resource(), server.prompt(), or widgets

This skill contains critical architecture decisions, security patterns, and common pitfalls.
Always consult the relevant reference files BEFORE implementing MCP features.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#22): mcp-builder]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/mcp-use/mcp-use/mcp-builder</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:mcp-use/mcp-use/mcp-builder</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #22
Installs: 172
Source: mcp-use/mcp-use
Description: Build Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers with mcp-use framework.
Use when creating MCP servers, defining tools/resources/prompts, working with mcp-use,
bootstrapping MCP projects, or when user mentions MCP development, tools, resources, or prompts.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#23): chatgpt-app-builder]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/mcp-use/mcp-use/chatgpt-app-builder</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:mcp-use/mcp-use/chatgpt-app-builder</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #23
Installs: 171
Source: mcp-use/mcp-use
Description: Build ChatGPT apps with interactive widgets using mcp-use and OpenAI Apps SDK.
Use when creating ChatGPT apps, building MCP servers with widgets, defining React widgets,
working with Apps SDK, or when user mentions ChatGPT widgets, mcp-use widgets, or Apps SDK development.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#27): agent-browser]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-browser</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-browser</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #27
Installs: 57
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Browser automation for AI agents via inference.sh. Navigate web pages, interact with elements using @e refs, take screenshots, record video. Capabilities: web scraping, form filling, clicking, typing, drag-drop, file upload, JavaScript execution. Use for: web automation, data extraction, testing, agent browsing, research. Triggers: browser, web automation, scrape, navigate, click, fill form, screenshot, browse web, playwright, headless browser, web agent, surf internet, record video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#28): seo-content-brief]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/seo-content-brief</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/seo-content-brief</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #28
Installs: 23
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: SEO content brief creation with keyword research, search intent analysis, and content structure. Covers SERP analysis, heading hierarchy, word count targets, and internal linking strategy. Use for: content briefs, SEO writing, blog strategy, content planning, keyword targeting. Triggers: seo content brief, content brief, seo brief, keyword research, search intent, content strategy, blog brief, seo writing, content planning, keyword targeting, serp analysis, content outline, seo article, blog seo]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#29): twitter-thread-creation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/twitter-thread-creation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/twitter-thread-creation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #29
Installs: 23
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Twitter/X thread writing with hook tweets, thread structure, and engagement optimization. Covers tweet formatting, character limits, media attachments, and posting strategies. Use for: Twitter threads, X posts, tweet storms, Twitter content, social media writing. Triggers: twitter thread, tweet thread, x thread, twitter post, tweet writing, thread creation, tweet storm, twitter content, x post, twitter writing, twitter hook, tweet formatting, thread structure]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#31): image-upscaling]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/image-upscaling</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/image-upscaling</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #31
Installs: 20
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Upscale and enhance images with Real-ESRGAN, Thera, Topaz, FLUX Upscaler via inference.sh CLI. Models: Real-ESRGAN, Thera (any size), FLUX Dev Upscaler, Topaz Image Upscaler. Use for: enhance low-res images, upscale AI art, restore old photos, increase resolution. Triggers: upscale image, image upscaler, enhance image, increase resolution, real esrgan, ai upscale, super resolution, image enhancement, upscaling, enlarge image, higher resolution, 4k upscale, hd upscale]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#32): logo-design-guide]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/logo-design-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/logo-design-guide</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #32
Installs: 20
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Logo design principles and AI image generation best practices for creating logos. Covers logo types, prompting techniques, scalability rules, and iteration workflows. Use for: brand identity, startup logos, app icons, favicons, logo concepts. Triggers: logo design, create logo, brand logo, logo generation, ai logo, logo maker, icon design, brand mark, logo concept, startup logo, app icon logo]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#35): youtube-thumbnail-design]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/youtube-thumbnail-design</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/youtube-thumbnail-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #35
Installs: 19
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: YouTube thumbnail design with specific dimensions, contrast rules, and mobile preview optimization. Covers safe zones, text placement, face expression psychology, and A/B testing. Use for: YouTube thumbnails, video cover images, click-through optimization. Triggers: youtube thumbnail, thumbnail design, video thumbnail, click through rate, ctr optimization, youtube cover, video cover image, thumbnail maker, thumbnail tips, youtube design, video preview image]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#36): find-skills]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/vercel-labs/skills/find-skills</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:vercel-labs/skills/find-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #36
Installs: 382
Source: vercel-labs/skills
Description: Helps users discover and install agent skills when they ask questions like "how do I do X", "find a skill for X", "is there a skill that can...", or express interest in extending capabilities. This skill should be used when the user is looking for functionality that might exist as an installable skill.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#39): llm-models]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/llm-models</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/llm-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #39
Installs: 17
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Access Claude, Gemini, Kimi, GLM and 100+ LLMs via inference.sh CLI using OpenRouter. Models: Claude Opus 4.5, Claude Sonnet 4.5, Claude Haiku 4.5, Gemini 3 Pro, Kimi K2, GLM-4.6, Intellect 3. One API for all models with automatic fallback and cost optimization. Use for: AI assistants, code generation, reasoning, agents, chat, content generation. Triggers: claude api, openrouter, llm api, claude sonnet, claude opus, gemini api, kimi, language model, gpt alternative, anthropic api, ai model api, llm access, chat api, claude alternative, openai alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#43): ai-product-photography]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/ai-product-photography</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/ai-product-photography</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #43
Installs: 15
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Generate professional AI product photography and commercial images. Models: FLUX, Imagen 3, Grok, Seedream for product shots, lifestyle images, mockups. Capabilities: studio lighting, lifestyle scenes, packaging, e-commerce photos. Use for: e-commerce, Amazon listings, Shopify, marketing, advertising, mockups. Triggers: product photography, product shot, commercial photography, e-commerce images, amazon product photo, shopify images, product mockup, studio product shot, lifestyle product image, advertising photo, packshot, product render, product image ai]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#44): ai-music-generation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/ai-music-generation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/ai-music-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #44
Installs: 15
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Generate AI music and songs with Diffrythm, Tencent Song Generation via inference.sh CLI. Models: Diffrythm (fast song generation), Tencent Song Generation (full songs with vocals). Capabilities: text-to-music, song generation, instrumental, lyrics to song, soundtrack creation. Use for: background music, social media content, game soundtracks, podcasts, royalty-free music. Triggers: music generation, ai music, generate song, ai composer, text to music, song generator, create music with ai, suno alternative, udio alternative, ai song, ai soundtrack, generate soundtrack, ai jingle, music ai, beat generator]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#45): ai-podcast-creation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/ai-podcast-creation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/ai-podcast-creation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #45
Installs: 15
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Create AI-powered podcasts with text-to-speech, music, and audio editing. Tools: Kokoro TTS, DIA TTS, Chatterbox, AI music generation, media merger. Capabilities: multi-voice conversations, background music, intro/outro, full episodes. Use for: podcast production, audiobooks, voice content, audio newsletters. Triggers: podcast, ai podcast, text to speech podcast, audio content, voice over, ai audiobook, multi voice, conversation ai, notebooklm alternative, audio generation, podcast automation, ai narrator, voice content, audio newsletter, podcast maker]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#46): product-changelog]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/product-changelog</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/product-changelog</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #46
Installs: 15
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Product changelog and release notes that users actually read. Covers categorization, user-facing language, visuals, and distribution. Use for: release notes, changelogs, product updates, feature announcements, versioning. Triggers: changelog, release notes, product update, version notes, what's new, feature announcement, product changelog, update log, release announcement, version release, product release, ship notes]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#47): typescript-advanced-types]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/wshobson/agents/typescript-advanced-types</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:new:wshobson/agents/typescript-advanced-types</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #47
Installs: 24
Source: wshobson/agents
Description: Master TypeScript's advanced type system including generics, conditional types, mapped types, template literals, and utility types for building type-safe applications. Use when implementing complex type logic, creating reusable type utilities, or ensuring compile-time type safety in TypeScript projects.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#30): agent-browser]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-browser</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topTrending:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-browser</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #30
Installs: 1486
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Browser automation for AI agents via inference.sh. Navigate web pages, interact with elements using @e refs, take screenshots, record video. Capabilities: web scraping, form filling, clicking, typing, drag-drop, file upload, JavaScript execution. Use for: web automation, data extraction, testing, agent browsing, research. Triggers: browser, web automation, scrape, navigate, click, fill form, screenshot, browse web, playwright, headless browser, web agent, surf internet, record video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#45): python-sdk]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/python-sdk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topTrending:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/python-sdk</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #45
Installs: 508
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Python SDK for inference.sh - run AI apps, build agents, and integrate with 150+ models. Package: inferencesh (pip install inferencesh). Supports sync/async, streaming, file uploads. Build agents with template or ad-hoc patterns, tool builder API, skills, and human approval. Use for: Python integration, AI apps, agent development, RAG pipelines, automation. Triggers: python sdk, inferencesh, pip install, python api, python client, async inference, python agent, tool builder python, programmatic ai, python integration, sdk python]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#46): widgets-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/widgets-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topTrending:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/widgets-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #46
Installs: 503
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: name: widgets-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#47): web-search]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/web-search</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topTrending:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/web-search</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #47
Installs: 501
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Web search and content extraction with Tavily and Exa via inference.sh CLI. Apps: Tavily Search, Tavily Extract, Exa Search, Exa Answer, Exa Extract. Capabilities: AI-powered search, content extraction, direct answers, research. Use for: research, RAG pipelines, fact-checking, content aggregation, agents. Triggers: web search, tavily, exa, search api, content extraction, research, internet search, ai search, search assistant, web scraping, rag, perplexity alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#50): agent-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topTrending:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #50
Installs: 487
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: name: agent-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank down (25 → 41): webapp-testing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/anthropics/skills/webapp-testing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:rank:anthropics/skills/webapp-testing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #25
Current rank: #41
Delta: -16
Installs: 12295 (prev 12184)
Source: anthropics/skills
Description: Toolkit for interacting with and testing local web applications using Playwright. Supports verifying frontend functionality, debugging UI behavior, capturing browser screenshots, and viewing browser logs.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank down (26 → 45): writing-plans]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/writing-plans</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:rank:obra/superpowers/writing-plans</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #26
Current rank: #45
Delta: -19
Installs: 12206 (prev 12055)
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when you have a spec or requirements for a multi-step task, before touching code]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank down (27 → 46): building-native-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/expo/skills/building-native-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:rank:expo/skills/building-native-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #27
Current rank: #46
Delta: -19
Installs: 11423 (prev 11322)
Source: expo/skills
Description: Complete guide for building beautiful apps with Expo Router. Covers fundamentals, styling, components, navigation, animations, patterns, and native tabs.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank down (28 → 47): test-driven-development]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/test-driven-development</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:rank:obra/superpowers/test-driven-development</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #28
Current rank: #47
Delta: -19
Installs: 11373 (prev 11247)
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when implementing any feature or bugfix, before writing implementation code]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank down (29 → 48): programmatic-seo]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/coreyhaines31/marketingskills/programmatic-seo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:rank:coreyhaines31/marketingskills/programmatic-seo</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #29
Current rank: #48
Delta: -19
Installs: 11042 (prev 10932)
Source: coreyhaines31/marketingskills
Description: When the user wants to create SEO-driven pages at scale using templates and data. Also use when the user mentions "programmatic SEO," "template pages," "pages at scale," "directory pages," "location pages," "[keyword] + [city] pages," "comparison pages," "integration pages," or "building many pages for SEO." For auditing existing SEO issues, see seo-audit.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank down (30 → 49): mcp-builder]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/anthropics/skills/mcp-builder</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:rank:anthropics/skills/mcp-builder</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #30
Current rank: #49
Delta: -19
Installs: 10972 (prev 10866)
Source: anthropics/skills
Description: Guide for creating high-quality MCP (Model Context Protocol) servers that enable LLMs to interact with external services through well-designed tools. Use when building MCP servers to integrate external APIs or services, whether in Python (FastMCP) or Node/TypeScript (MCP SDK).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank down (31 → 50): content-strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/coreyhaines31/marketingskills/content-strategy</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:rank:coreyhaines31/marketingskills/content-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #31
Current rank: #50
Delta: -19
Installs: 10917 (prev 10811)
Source: coreyhaines31/marketingskills
Description: When the user wants to plan a content strategy, decide what content to create, or figure out what topics to cover. Also use when the user mentions "content strategy," "what should I write about," "content ideas," "blog strategy," "topic clusters," or "content planning." For writing individual pieces, see copywriting. For SEO-specific audits, see seo-audit.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank up (50 → 25): azure-observability]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-observability</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topAllTime:rank:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-observability</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #50
Current rank: #25
Delta: +25
Installs: 12308 (prev 7898)
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Azure Observability Services including Azure Monitor, Application Insights, Log Analytics, Alerts, and Workbooks. Provides metrics, APM, distributed tracing, KQL queries, and interactive reports.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (1 → 19): agent-tools]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-tools</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:rank:1nfsh-s3/skills/agent-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #1
Current rank: #19
Delta: -18
Installs: 423 (prev 870)
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Run 150+ AI apps via inference.sh CLI - image generation, video creation, LLMs, search, 3D, Twitter automation. Models: FLUX, Veo, Gemini, Grok, Claude, Seedance, OmniHuman, Tavily, Exa, OpenRouter, and many more. Use when running AI apps, generating images/videos, calling LLMs, web search, or automating Twitter. Triggers: inference.sh, infsh, ai model, run ai, serverless ai, ai api, flux, veo, claude api, image generation, video generation, openrouter, tavily, exa search, twitter api, grok]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (2 → 6): azure-storage]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-storage</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T18:58:18.604Z:topHot:rank:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-storage</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:58:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #2
Current rank: #6
Delta: -4
Installs: 626 (prev 834)
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Azure Storage Services including Blob Storage, File Shares, Queue Storage, Table Storage, and Data Lake. Provides object storage, SMB file shares, async messaging, NoSQL key-value, and big data analytics capabilities. Includes access tiers (hot, cool, archive) and lifecycle management.]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>