<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Skills.sh Feed</title>
        <link>https://skills.sh</link>
        <description>Latest skill data from skills.sh</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Daily] Skills.sh snapshot (2026-02-20)]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:snapshot</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Daily snapshot.
Providers: skills.sh
All Time skills: 30747
Trending skills: 12105
Hot skills: 1468
Top All Time: find-skills (274717)
Top Trending: find-skills (8978)
Top Hot: agent-tools (870)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#50): azure-observability]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-observability</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topAllTime:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-observability</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #50
Installs: 7898
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Azure Observability Services including Azure Monitor, Application Insights, Log Analytics, Alerts, and Workbooks. Provides metrics, APM, distributed tracing, KQL queries, and interactive reports.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#10): azure-ai]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-ai</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #10
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Use for Azure AI: Search, Speech, OpenAI, Document Intelligence. Helps with search, vector/hybrid search, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, transcription, OCR. USE FOR: AI Search, query search, vector search, hybrid search, semantic search, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, transcribe, OCR, convert text to speech. DO NOT USE FOR: Function apps/Functions (use azure-functions), databases (azure-postgres/azure-kusto), general Azure resources.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#11): azure-resource-lookup]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-lookup</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-lookup</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #11
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: List, find, and show Azure resources. Answers "list my VMs", "show my storage accounts", "list websites",
"find container apps", "what resources do I have", and similar queries for any Azure resource type.
USE FOR: list resources, list virtual machines, list VMs, list storage accounts, list websites, list web apps,
list container apps, show resources, find resources, what resources do I have, list resources in resource group,
list resources in subscription, find resources by tag, find orphaned resources, resource inventory,
count resources by type, cross-subscription resource query, Azure Resource Graph, resource discovery,
list container registries, list SQL servers, list Key Vaults, show resource groups, list app services,
find resources across subscriptions, find unattached disks, tag analysis.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), creating or modifying resources,
cost optimization (use azure-cost-optimization), writing application code, non-Azure clouds.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#12): azure-validate]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-validate</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-validate</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #12
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Pre-deployment validation checkpoint. Run deep checks to ensure your application is ready for Azure deployment. Validates configuration, infrastructure, permissions, and prerequisites.
USE FOR: validate my app, check deployment readiness, run preflight checks, verify configuration, check if ready to deploy, validate azure.yaml, validate Bicep, test before deploying, troubleshoot deployment errors.
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or building apps (use azure-prepare), executing deployments (use azure-deploy).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#13): azure-postgres]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-postgres</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-postgres</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #13
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Create new Azure Database for PostgreSQL Flexible Server instances and configure passwordless authentication with Microsoft Entra ID. Set up developer access, managed identities for apps, group-based permissions, and migrate from password-based to Entra ID authentication. Trigger phrases include "passwordless for postgres", "entra id postgres", "azure ad postgres authentication", "postgres managed identity", "migrate postgres to passwordless".]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#14): entra-app-registration]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/entra-app-registration</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/entra-app-registration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #14
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Guides Microsoft Entra ID app registration, OAuth 2.0 authentication, and MSAL integration.
USE FOR: create app registration, register Azure AD app, configure OAuth, set up authentication, add API permissions, generate service principal, MSAL example, console app auth, Entra ID setup, Azure AD authentication.
DO NOT USE FOR: Azure RBAC or role assignments (use azure-rbac), Key Vault secrets (use azure-keyvault-expiration-audit), Azure resource security (use azure-security).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#15): azure-aigateway]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-aigateway</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-aigateway</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #15
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Configure Azure API Management (APIM) as AI Gateway to secure, observe, control AI models, MCP servers, agents. Helps with rate limiting, semantic caching, content safety, load balancing.
USE FOR: AI Gateway, APIM, setup gateway, configure gateway, add gateway, model gateway, MCP server, rate limit, token limit, semantic cache, content safety, load balance, OpenAPI import, convert API to MCP.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploy models (use microsoft-foundry), Azure Functions (use azure-functions), databases (use azure-postgres).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#16): azure-resource-visualizer]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-visualizer</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-visualizer</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #16
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Analyze Azure resource groups and generate detailed Mermaid architecture diagrams showing the relationships between individual resources.
USE FOR: create architecture diagram, visualize Azure resources, show resource relationships, generate Mermaid diagram, analyze resource group, diagram my resources, architecture visualization, resource topology, map Azure infrastructure
DO NOT USE FOR: creating/modifying resources (use azure-deploy), security scanning (use azure-security), performance troubleshooting (use azure-diagnostics), code generation (use relevant service skill)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#17): azure-compliance]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-compliance</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-compliance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #17
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Comprehensive Azure compliance and security auditing capabilities including best practices assessment,
Key Vault expiration monitoring, and resource configuration validation.
USE FOR: compliance scan, security audit, azqr, Azure best practices, Key Vault expiration check,
compliance assessment, resource review, configuration validation, expired certificates, expiring secrets,
orphaned resources, policy compliance, security posture evaluation.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), cost analysis alone (use azure-cost-optimization),
active security hardening (use azure-security-hardening), general Azure Advisor queries (use azure-observability).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#18): azure-diagnostics]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-diagnostics</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-diagnostics</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #18
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Debug and troubleshoot production issues on Azure. Covers Container Apps diagnostics, log analysis with KQL, health checks, and common issue resolution for image pulls, cold starts, and health probes.
USE FOR: debug production issues, troubleshoot container apps, analyze logs with KQL, fix image pull failures, resolve cold start issues, investigate health probe failures, check resource health, view application logs, find root cause of errors
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying applications (use azure-deploy), creating new resources (use azure-prepare), setting up monitoring (use azure-observability), cost optimization (use azure-cost-optimization)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#19): azure-kusto]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-kusto</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-kusto</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #19
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Query and analyze data in Azure Data Explorer (Kusto/ADX) using KQL for log analytics, telemetry, and time series analysis.
USE FOR: KQL queries, Kusto database queries, Azure Data Explorer, ADX clusters, log analytics, time series data, IoT telemetry, anomaly detection
DO NOT USE FOR: SQL databases (use azure-postgres), NoSQL queries (use azure-storage), Elasticsearch, AWS analytics tools]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#2): azure-storage]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-storage</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-storage</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #2
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Azure Storage Services including Blob Storage, File Shares, Queue Storage, Table Storage, and Data Lake. Provides object storage, SMB file shares, async messaging, NoSQL key-value, and big data analytics capabilities. Includes access tiers (hot, cool, archive) and lifecycle management.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#23): seedance2-api]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/hexiaochun/seedance2-api/seedance2-api</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:hexiaochun/seedance2-api/seedance2-api</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #23
Installs: 56
Source: hexiaochun/seedance2-api
Description: Out-of-the-box Seedance 2.0 API skill — just one API key to generate AI videos. Builds storyboards, generates reference images with Seedream 4.5, submits video tasks, and polls results. Supports both MCP and standalone Python script mode. Use when the user mentions seedance, AI video, storyboard, or video generation.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#26): widgets-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/widgets-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/widgets-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #26
Installs: 39
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: name: widgets-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#27): chat-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/chat-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/chat-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #27
Installs: 37
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: name: chat-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#28): web-search]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/web-search</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/web-search</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #28
Installs: 34
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Web search and content extraction with Tavily and Exa via inference.sh CLI. Apps: Tavily Search, Tavily Extract, Exa Search, Exa Answer, Exa Extract. Capabilities: AI-powered search, content extraction, direct answers, research. Use for: research, RAG pipelines, fact-checking, content aggregation, agents. Triggers: web search, tavily, exa, search api, content extraction, research, internet search, ai search, search assistant, web scraping, rag, perplexity alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#3): appinsights-instrumentation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/appinsights-instrumentation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/appinsights-instrumentation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #3
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Guidance for instrumenting webapps with Azure Application Insights. Provides telemetry patterns, SDK setup, and configuration references.
USE FOR: how to instrument app, App Insights SDK, telemetry patterns, what is App Insights, Application Insights guidance, instrumentation examples, APM best practices.
DO NOT USE FOR: adding App Insights to my app (use azure-prepare), add telemetry to my project (use azure-prepare), add monitoring (use azure-prepare). This skill provides guidance—azure-prepare orchestrates component changes.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#36): case-study-writing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/case-study-writing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/case-study-writing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #36
Installs: 28
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: B2B case study writing with STAR framework, data visualization, and research. Covers structure, customer quotes, metrics presentation, and distribution formats. Use for: customer success stories, portfolio pieces, sales enablement, marketing content. Triggers: case study, customer story, success story, b2b case study, client testimonial, customer case study, portfolio case study, use case, customer win, results story]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#39): video-prompting-guide]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/video-prompting-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/video-prompting-guide</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #39
Installs: 27
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Best practices and techniques for writing effective AI video generation prompts. Covers: Veo, Seedance, Wan, Grok, Kling, Runway, Pika, Sora prompting strategies. Learn: shot types, camera movements, lighting, pacing, style keywords, negative prompts. Use for: improving video quality, getting consistent results, professional video prompts. Triggers: video prompt, how to prompt video, veo prompts, video generation tips, better ai video, video prompt engineering, video prompt guide, video prompt template, ai video tips, video prompt best practices, video prompt examples, cinematography prompts]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#4): azure-deploy]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-deploy</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-deploy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #4
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Execute deployment to Azure. Final step after preparation and validation. Runs azd up, azd deploy, or infrastructure provisioning commands.
USE FOR: run azd up, run azd deploy, execute deployment, provision infrastructure, push to production, go live, ship it, deploy web app, deploy container app, deploy static site, deploy Azure Functions, bicep deploy, terraform apply.
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or building apps (use azure-prepare), validating before deploy (use azure-validate).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#42): related-skill]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/related-skill</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/related-skill</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #42
Installs: 25
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Discover and install related skills from inference.sh skill registry. Helps find complementary skills for your AI workflow. Use for: skill discovery, workflow expansion, capability exploration. Triggers: related skills, find skills, skill discovery, complementary skills, expand workflow, more capabilities, similar skills, skill suggestions]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#48): landing-page-design]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/landing-page-design</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:1nfsh-s3/skills/landing-page-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #48
Installs: 24
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Landing page conversion optimization with layout rules, hero section design, and CTA psychology. Covers above-the-fold formula, social proof placement, mobile design, and F-pattern reading. Use for: startup landing pages, product pages, SaaS marketing, conversion optimization. Triggers: landing page, hero section, above the fold, conversion optimization, landing page design, cta button, hero image, landing page layout, saas landing page, product page design, conversion rate, landing page best practices]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#5): azure-rbac]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-rbac</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-rbac</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #5
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Helps users find the right Azure RBAC role for an identity with least privilege access, then generate CLI commands and Bicep code to assign it.
USE FOR: "what role should I assign", "least privilege role", "RBAC role for", "role to read blobs", "role for managed identity", "custom role definition", "assign role to identity".
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or configuring managed identities, or general Azure security hardening; those are out of scope for this role-selection skill.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#6): azure-prepare]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-prepare</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-prepare</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #6
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Default entry point for Azure application development. Invoke this skill for ANY application work related to Azure: creating apps, building features, adding components, updating code, migrating, or modernizing. Analyzes your project and prepares it for Azure deployment by generating infrastructure code (Bicep/Terraform), azure.yaml configuration, and Dockerfiles.
USE FOR: create an app, build a web app, create API, create frontend, create backend, add a feature, build a service, make an application, develop a project, migrate my app, modernize my code, update my application, add database, add authentication, add caching, deploy to Azure, host on Azure, Azure with Terraform (defaults to azd+Terraform), Azure with azd, generate azure.yaml, generate Bicep or Terraform, prepare Azure Functions.
DO NOT USE FOR: only validating an already-prepared app (use azure-validate), only running azd up/deploy (use azure-deploy), pure Terraform without azd (prefer azd+Terraform).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#7): microsoft-foundry]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/microsoft-foundry</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/microsoft-foundry</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #7
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Use this skill to work with Microsoft Foundry (Azure AI Foundry): deploy AI models from catalog, build RAG applications with knowledge indexes, create and evaluate AI agents, manage RBAC permissions and role assignments, manage quotas and capacity, create Foundry resources.
USE FOR: Microsoft Foundry, AI Foundry, deploy model, model catalog, RAG, knowledge index, create agent, evaluate agent, agent monitoring, create Foundry project, new Foundry project, set up Foundry, onboard to Foundry, provision Foundry infrastructure, create Foundry resource, create AI Services, multi-service resource, AIServices kind, register resource provider, enable Cognitive Services, setup AI Services account, create resource group for Foundry, RBAC, role assignment, managed identity, service principal, permissions, quota, capacity, TPM, deployment failure, QuotaExceeded.
DO NOT USE FOR: Azure Functions (use azure-functions), App Service (use azure-create-app), generic Azure resource creation (use azure-create-app).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#8): azure-cost-optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-cost-optimization</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-cost-optimization</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #8
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Identify and quantify cost savings across Azure subscriptions by analyzing actual costs,
utilization metrics, and generating actionable optimization recommendations. USE FOR:
optimize Azure costs, reduce Azure spending, reduce Azure expenses, analyze Azure costs,
find cost savings, generate cost optimization report, find orphaned resources, rightsize VMs,
cost analysis, reduce waste, Azure spending analysis, find unused resources, optimize Redis
costs. DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), general Azure diagnostics
(use azure-diagnostics), security issues (use azure-security)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#9): azure-observability]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-observability</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-observability</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #9
Installs: 834
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Azure Observability Services including Azure Monitor, Application Insights, Log Analytics, Alerts, and Workbooks. Provides metrics, APM, distributed tracing, KQL queries, and interactive reports.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#10): azure-validate]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-validate</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-validate</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #10
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Pre-deployment validation checkpoint. Run deep checks to ensure your application is ready for Azure deployment. Validates configuration, infrastructure, permissions, and prerequisites.
USE FOR: validate my app, check deployment readiness, run preflight checks, verify configuration, check if ready to deploy, validate azure.yaml, validate Bicep, test before deploying, troubleshoot deployment errors.
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or building apps (use azure-prepare), executing deployments (use azure-deploy).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#11): azure-compliance]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-compliance</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-compliance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #11
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Comprehensive Azure compliance and security auditing capabilities including best practices assessment,
Key Vault expiration monitoring, and resource configuration validation.
USE FOR: compliance scan, security audit, azqr, Azure best practices, Key Vault expiration check,
compliance assessment, resource review, configuration validation, expired certificates, expiring secrets,
orphaned resources, policy compliance, security posture evaluation.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), cost analysis alone (use azure-cost-optimization),
active security hardening (use azure-security-hardening), general Azure Advisor queries (use azure-observability).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#12): azure-storage]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-storage</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-storage</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #12
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Azure Storage Services including Blob Storage, File Shares, Queue Storage, Table Storage, and Data Lake. Provides object storage, SMB file shares, async messaging, NoSQL key-value, and big data analytics capabilities. Includes access tiers (hot, cool, archive) and lifecycle management.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#13): azure-kusto]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-kusto</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-kusto</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #13
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Query and analyze data in Azure Data Explorer (Kusto/ADX) using KQL for log analytics, telemetry, and time series analysis.
USE FOR: KQL queries, Kusto database queries, Azure Data Explorer, ADX clusters, log analytics, time series data, IoT telemetry, anomaly detection
DO NOT USE FOR: SQL databases (use azure-postgres), NoSQL queries (use azure-storage), Elasticsearch, AWS analytics tools]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#14): appinsights-instrumentation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/appinsights-instrumentation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/appinsights-instrumentation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #14
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Guidance for instrumenting webapps with Azure Application Insights. Provides telemetry patterns, SDK setup, and configuration references.
USE FOR: how to instrument app, App Insights SDK, telemetry patterns, what is App Insights, Application Insights guidance, instrumentation examples, APM best practices.
DO NOT USE FOR: adding App Insights to my app (use azure-prepare), add telemetry to my project (use azure-prepare), add monitoring (use azure-prepare). This skill provides guidance—azure-prepare orchestrates component changes.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#15): azure-deploy]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-deploy</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-deploy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #15
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Execute deployment to Azure. Final step after preparation and validation. Runs azd up, azd deploy, or infrastructure provisioning commands.
USE FOR: run azd up, run azd deploy, execute deployment, provision infrastructure, push to production, go live, ship it, deploy web app, deploy container app, deploy static site, deploy Azure Functions, bicep deploy, terraform apply.
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or building apps (use azure-prepare), validating before deploy (use azure-validate).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#16): azure-prepare]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-prepare</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-prepare</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #16
Installs: 7767
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Default entry point for Azure application development. Invoke this skill for ANY application work related to Azure: creating apps, building features, adding components, updating code, migrating, or modernizing. Analyzes your project and prepares it for Azure deployment by generating infrastructure code (Bicep/Terraform), azure.yaml configuration, and Dockerfiles.
USE FOR: create an app, build a web app, create API, create frontend, create backend, add a feature, build a service, make an application, develop a project, migrate my app, modernize my code, update my application, add database, add authentication, add caching, deploy to Azure, host on Azure, Azure with Terraform (defaults to azd+Terraform), Azure with azd, generate azure.yaml, generate Bicep or Terraform, prepare Azure Functions.
DO NOT USE FOR: only validating an already-prepared app (use azure-validate), only running azd up/deploy (use azure-deploy), pure Terraform without azd (prefer azd+Terraform).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#17): azure-postgres]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-postgres</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-postgres</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #17
Installs: 7767
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Create new Azure Database for PostgreSQL Flexible Server instances and configure passwordless authentication with Microsoft Entra ID. Set up developer access, managed identities for apps, group-based permissions, and migrate from password-based to Entra ID authentication. Trigger phrases include "passwordless for postgres", "entra id postgres", "azure ad postgres authentication", "postgres managed identity", "migrate postgres to passwordless".]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#18): entra-app-registration]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/entra-app-registration</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/entra-app-registration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #18
Installs: 7767
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Guides Microsoft Entra ID app registration, OAuth 2.0 authentication, and MSAL integration.
USE FOR: create app registration, register Azure AD app, configure OAuth, set up authentication, add API permissions, generate service principal, MSAL example, console app auth, Entra ID setup, Azure AD authentication.
DO NOT USE FOR: Azure RBAC or role assignments (use azure-rbac), Key Vault secrets (use azure-keyvault-expiration-audit), Azure resource security (use azure-security).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#19): microsoft-foundry]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/microsoft-foundry</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/microsoft-foundry</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #19
Installs: 7767
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Use this skill to work with Microsoft Foundry (Azure AI Foundry): deploy AI models from catalog, build RAG applications with knowledge indexes, create and evaluate AI agents, manage RBAC permissions and role assignments, manage quotas and capacity, create Foundry resources.
USE FOR: Microsoft Foundry, AI Foundry, deploy model, model catalog, RAG, knowledge index, create agent, evaluate agent, agent monitoring, create Foundry project, new Foundry project, set up Foundry, onboard to Foundry, provision Foundry infrastructure, create Foundry resource, create AI Services, multi-service resource, AIServices kind, register resource provider, enable Cognitive Services, setup AI Services account, create resource group for Foundry, RBAC, role assignment, managed identity, service principal, permissions, quota, capacity, TPM, deployment failure, QuotaExceeded.
DO NOT USE FOR: Azure Functions (use azure-functions), App Service (use azure-create-app), generic Azure resource creation (use azure-create-app).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#2): azure-cost-optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-cost-optimization</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-cost-optimization</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #2
Installs: 7770
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Identify and quantify cost savings across Azure subscriptions by analyzing actual costs,
utilization metrics, and generating actionable optimization recommendations. USE FOR:
optimize Azure costs, reduce Azure spending, reduce Azure expenses, analyze Azure costs,
find cost savings, generate cost optimization report, find orphaned resources, rightsize VMs,
cost analysis, reduce waste, Azure spending analysis, find unused resources, optimize Redis
costs. DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), general Azure diagnostics
(use azure-diagnostics), security issues (use azure-security)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#3): azure-observability]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-observability</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-observability</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #3
Installs: 7769
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Azure Observability Services including Azure Monitor, Application Insights, Log Analytics, Alerts, and Workbooks. Provides metrics, APM, distributed tracing, KQL queries, and interactive reports.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#4): azure-rbac]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-rbac</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-rbac</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #4
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Helps users find the right Azure RBAC role for an identity with least privilege access, then generate CLI commands and Bicep code to assign it.
USE FOR: "what role should I assign", "least privilege role", "RBAC role for", "role to read blobs", "role for managed identity", "custom role definition", "assign role to identity".
DO NOT USE FOR: creating or configuring managed identities, or general Azure security hardening; those are out of scope for this role-selection skill.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#5): azure-resource-lookup]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-lookup</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-lookup</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #5
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: List, find, and show Azure resources. Answers "list my VMs", "show my storage accounts", "list websites",
"find container apps", "what resources do I have", and similar queries for any Azure resource type.
USE FOR: list resources, list virtual machines, list VMs, list storage accounts, list websites, list web apps,
list container apps, show resources, find resources, what resources do I have, list resources in resource group,
list resources in subscription, find resources by tag, find orphaned resources, resource inventory,
count resources by type, cross-subscription resource query, Azure Resource Graph, resource discovery,
list container registries, list SQL servers, list Key Vaults, show resource groups, list app services,
find resources across subscriptions, find unattached disks, tag analysis.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying resources (use azure-deploy), creating or modifying resources,
cost optimization (use azure-cost-optimization), writing application code, non-Azure clouds.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#6): azure-resource-visualizer]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-visualizer</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-resource-visualizer</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #6
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Analyze Azure resource groups and generate detailed Mermaid architecture diagrams showing the relationships between individual resources.
USE FOR: create architecture diagram, visualize Azure resources, show resource relationships, generate Mermaid diagram, analyze resource group, diagram my resources, architecture visualization, resource topology, map Azure infrastructure
DO NOT USE FOR: creating/modifying resources (use azure-deploy), security scanning (use azure-security), performance troubleshooting (use azure-diagnostics), code generation (use relevant service skill)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#7): azure-ai]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-ai</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #7
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Use for Azure AI: Search, Speech, OpenAI, Document Intelligence. Helps with search, vector/hybrid search, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, transcription, OCR. USE FOR: AI Search, query search, vector search, hybrid search, semantic search, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, transcribe, OCR, convert text to speech. DO NOT USE FOR: Function apps/Functions (use azure-functions), databases (azure-postgres/azure-kusto), general Azure resources.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#8): azure-aigateway]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-aigateway</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-aigateway</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #8
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Configure Azure API Management (APIM) as AI Gateway to secure, observe, control AI models, MCP servers, agents. Helps with rate limiting, semantic caching, content safety, load balancing.
USE FOR: AI Gateway, APIM, setup gateway, configure gateway, add gateway, model gateway, MCP server, rate limit, token limit, semantic cache, content safety, load balance, OpenAPI import, convert API to MCP.
DO NOT USE FOR: deploy models (use microsoft-foundry), Azure Functions (use azure-functions), databases (use azure-postgres).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#9): azure-diagnostics]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-diagnostics</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topTrending:new:microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure/azure-diagnostics</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #9
Installs: 7768
Source: microsoft/github-copilot-for-azure
Description: Debug and troubleshoot production issues on Azure. Covers Container Apps diagnostics, log analysis with KQL, health checks, and common issue resolution for image pulls, cold starts, and health probes.
USE FOR: debug production issues, troubleshoot container apps, analyze logs with KQL, fix image pull failures, resolve cold start issues, investigate health probe failures, check resource health, view application logs, find root cause of errors
DO NOT USE FOR: deploying applications (use azure-deploy), creating new resources (use azure-prepare), setting up monitoring (use azure-observability), cost optimization (use azure-cost-optimization)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (11 → 25): javascript-sdk]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/javascript-sdk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:rank:1nfsh-s3/skills/javascript-sdk</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #11
Current rank: #25
Delta: -14
Installs: 39 (prev 14)
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: JavaScript/TypeScript SDK for inference.sh - run AI apps, build agents, integrate 150+ models. Package: @inferencesh/sdk (npm install). Full TypeScript support, streaming, file uploads. Build agents with template or ad-hoc patterns, tool builder API, skills, human approval. Use for: JavaScript integration, TypeScript, Node.js, React, Next.js, frontend apps. Triggers: javascript sdk, typescript sdk, npm install, node.js api, js client, react ai, next.js ai, frontend sdk, @inferencesh/sdk, typescript agent, browser sdk, js integration]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (12 → 49): competitor-teardown]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/competitor-teardown</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:rank:1nfsh-s3/skills/competitor-teardown</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #12
Current rank: #49
Delta: -37
Installs: 24 (prev 14)
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Structured competitive analysis with feature matrices, SWOT, positioning maps, and UX review. Covers research frameworks, pricing comparison, review mining, and visual deliverables. Use for: market research, competitive intelligence, investor decks, product strategy, sales enablement. Triggers: competitor analysis, competitive analysis, competitor teardown, market research, competitive intelligence, swot analysis, competitor comparison, market landscape, competitor review, competitive landscape, feature comparison, market positioning]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (13 → 40): video-ad-specs]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/video-ad-specs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:rank:1nfsh-s3/skills/video-ad-specs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #13
Current rank: #40
Delta: -27
Installs: 27 (prev 14)
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Video ad creation with exact platform-specific specs for TikTok, Instagram, YouTube, Facebook, LinkedIn. Covers dimensions, duration limits, AIDA framework, and caption requirements. Use for: video ads, social media ads, paid media creative, video marketing, ad production. Triggers: video ad, social media ad, tiktok ad, instagram ad, youtube ad, facebook ad, linkedin ad, video creative, ad specs, paid media, video marketing, ad production, reels ad, stories ad, pre roll, bumper ad]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (15 → 32): press-release-writing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/press-release-writing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:rank:1nfsh-s3/skills/press-release-writing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #15
Current rank: #32
Delta: -17
Installs: 32 (prev 13)
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Press release writing in AP style with inverted pyramid structure. Covers formatting, datelines, quotes, boilerplates, and fact-checking. Use for: product launches, funding announcements, partnerships, company news, events. Triggers: press release, pr writing, media release, news release, announcement, product launch announcement, funding announcement, company news, media advisory, ap style, press statement, news wire]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (16 → 38): storyboard-creation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/1nfsh-s3/skills/storyboard-creation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20T13:11:57.993Z:topHot:rank:1nfsh-s3/skills/storyboard-creation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #16
Current rank: #38
Delta: -22
Installs: 27 (prev 13)
Source: 1nfsh-s3/skills
Description: Film and video storyboarding with shot vocabulary, continuity rules, and panel layout. Covers shot types, camera angles, movement, 180-degree rule, and annotation format. Use for: video planning, film pre-production, ad storyboards, music video planning, animation. Triggers: storyboard, storyboarding, shot list, film planning, video planning, pre production, shot composition, camera angles, scene planning, visual script, animatic, storyboard panels, video storyboard]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>