<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Skills.sh Feed</title>
        <link>https://skills.sh</link>
        <description>Latest skill data from skills.sh</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Daily] Skills.sh snapshot (2026-02-19)]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:snapshot</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Daily snapshot.
Providers: skills.sh
All Time skills: 30024
Trending skills: 10370
Hot skills: 1641
Top All Time: find-skills (265641)
Top Trending: find-skills (10180)
Top Hot: agent-tools (480)]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] New entry (#50): receiving-code-review]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/receiving-code-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topAllTime:new:obra/superpowers/receiving-code-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in All Time leaderboard.
Rank: #50
Installs: 7574
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when receiving code review feedback, before implementing suggestions, especially if feedback seems unclear or technically questionable - requires technical rigor and verification, not performative agreement or blind implementation]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#1): agent-tools]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-3/skills/agent-tools</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-3/skills/agent-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #1
Installs: 480
Source: inference-sh-3/skills
Description: Run 150+ AI apps via inference.sh CLI - image generation, video creation, LLMs, search, 3D, Twitter automation. Models: FLUX, Veo, Gemini, Grok, Claude, Seedance, OmniHuman, Tavily, Exa, OpenRouter, and many more. Use when running AI apps, generating images/videos, calling LLMs, web search, or automating Twitter. Triggers: inference.sh, infsh, ai model, run ai, serverless ai, ai api, flux, veo, claude api, image generation, video generation, openrouter, tavily, exa search, twitter api, grok]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#10): ai-video-generation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/ai-video-generation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/ai-video-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #10
Installs: 72
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Generate AI videos with Google Veo, Seedance, Wan, Grok and 40+ models via inference.sh CLI. Models: Veo 3.1, Veo 3, Seedance 1.5 Pro, Wan 2.5, Grok Imagine Video, OmniHuman, Fabric, HunyuanVideo. Capabilities: text-to-video, image-to-video, lipsync, avatar animation, video upscaling, foley sound. Use for: social media videos, marketing content, explainer videos, product demos, AI avatars. Triggers: video generation, ai video, text to video, image to video, veo, animate image, video from image, ai animation, video generator, generate video, t2v, i2v, ai video maker, create video with ai, runway alternative, pika alternative, sora alternative, kling alternative]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#13): ui-animation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/mblode/agent-skills/ui-animation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:mblode/agent-skills/ui-animation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #13
Installs: 31
Source: mblode/agent-skills
Description: Guidelines and examples for UI motion and animation. Use when designing, implementing, or reviewing motion, easing, timing, and reduced-motion behaviour.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#14): pitch-deck-visuals]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/pitch-deck-visuals</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/pitch-deck-visuals</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #14
Installs: 28
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Investor pitch deck structure with slide-by-slide framework, visual design rules, and data presentation. Covers the 12-slide framework, chart types, team slides, and common investor turn-offs. Use for: fundraising decks, investor presentations, startup pitch, demo day, grant proposals. Triggers: pitch deck, investor deck, startup pitch, fundraising deck, demo day, pitch presentation, investor presentation, seed deck, series a deck, pitch slides, startup presentation, vc pitch, investor meeting]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#15): m15-anti-pattern]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/zhanghandong/rust-skills/m15-anti-pattern</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:zhanghandong/rust-skills/m15-anti-pattern</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #15
Installs: 28
Source: zhanghandong/rust-skills
Description: Use when reviewing code for anti-patterns. Keywords: anti-pattern, common mistake, pitfall, code smell, bad practice, code review, is this an anti-pattern, better way to do this, common mistake to avoid, why is this bad, idiomatic way, beginner mistake, fighting borrow checker, clone everywhere, unwrap in production, should I refactor, 反模式, 常见错误, 代码异味, 最佳实践, 地道写法]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#19): data-visualization]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/anthropics/knowledge-work-plugins/data-visualization</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:anthropics/knowledge-work-plugins/data-visualization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #19
Installs: 30
Source: anthropics/knowledge-work-plugins
Description: Create effective data visualizations with Python (matplotlib, seaborn, plotly). Use when building charts, choosing the right chart type for a dataset, creating publication-quality figures, or applying design principles like accessibility and color theory.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#2): ai-image-generation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/ai-image-generation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/ai-image-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #2
Installs: 84
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Generate AI images with FLUX, Gemini, Grok, Seedream, Reve and 50+ models via inference.sh CLI. Models: FLUX Dev LoRA, FLUX.2 Klein LoRA, Gemini 3 Pro Image, Grok Imagine, Seedream 4.5, Reve, ImagineArt. Capabilities: text-to-image, image-to-image, inpainting, LoRA, image editing, upscaling, text rendering. Use for: AI art, product mockups, concept art, social media graphics, marketing visuals, illustrations. Triggers: flux, image generation, ai image, text to image, stable diffusion, generate image, ai art, midjourney alternative, dall-e alternative, text2img, t2i, image generator, ai picture, create image with ai, generative ai, ai illustration, grok image, gemini image]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#20): ai-voice-cloning]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/ai-voice-cloning</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/ai-voice-cloning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #20
Installs: 27
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: AI voice generation, text-to-speech, and voice synthesis via inference.sh CLI. Models: Kokoro TTS, DIA, Chatterbox, Higgs, VibeVoice for natural speech. Capabilities: multiple voices, emotions, accents, long-form narration, conversation. Use for: voiceovers, audiobooks, podcasts, video narration, accessibility. Triggers: voice cloning, tts, text to speech, ai voice, voice generation, voice synthesis, voice over, narration, speech synthesis, ai narrator, elevenlabs alternative, natural voice, realistic speech, voice ai]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#21): google-search-browser-use]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/grasseed/google-search-browser-use/google-search-browser-use</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:grasseed/google-search-browser-use/google-search-browser-use</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #21
Installs: 24
Source: grasseed/google-search-browser-use
Description: Use browser-use to perform Google searches, open results, and extract key information from live pages. Use when the user asks to "search Google", "look this up on Google", or needs current web results via a real browser session (often to avoid bot blocks).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#22): ai-podcast-creation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/ai-podcast-creation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/ai-podcast-creation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #22
Installs: 22
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Create AI-powered podcasts with text-to-speech, music, and audio editing. Tools: Kokoro TTS, DIA TTS, Chatterbox, AI music generation, media merger. Capabilities: multi-voice conversations, background music, intro/outro, full episodes. Use for: podcast production, audiobooks, voice content, audio newsletters. Triggers: podcast, ai podcast, text to speech podcast, audio content, voice over, ai audiobook, multi voice, conversation ai, notebooklm alternative, audio generation, podcast automation, ai narrator, voice content, audio newsletter, podcast maker]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#23): super-search]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/supermemoryai/claude-supermemory/super-search</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:supermemoryai/claude-supermemory/super-search</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #23
Installs: 31
Source: supermemoryai/claude-supermemory
Description: Search your coding memory. Use when user asks about past work, previous sessions, how something was implemented, what they worked on before, or wants to recall information from earlier sessions.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#24): music-downloader]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/nymbo/skills/music-downloader</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:nymbo/skills/music-downloader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #24
Installs: 30
Source: nymbo/skills
Description: This skill should be used when users need to download audio or music from online platforms like YouTube, SoundCloud, Spotify, or other streaming services. It provides yt-dlp and spotdl command templates for high-quality audio extraction, playlist downloads, metadata embedding, and multi-platform support.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#25): fastapi-python]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/mindrally/skills/fastapi-python</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:mindrally/skills/fastapi-python</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #25
Installs: 26
Source: mindrally/skills
Description: Expert in FastAPI Python development with best practices for APIs and async operations]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#26): xlsx]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/tfriedel/claude-office-skills/xlsx</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:tfriedel/claude-office-skills/xlsx</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #26
Installs: 22
Source: tfriedel/claude-office-skills
Description: Comprehensive spreadsheet creation, editing, and analysis with support for formulas, formatting, data analysis, and visualization. When Claude needs to work with spreadsheets (.xlsx, .xlsm, .csv, .tsv, etc) for: (1) Creating new spreadsheets with formulas and formatting, (2) Reading or analyzing data, (3) Modify existing spreadsheets while preserving formulas, (4) Data analysis and visualization in spreadsheets, or (5) Recalculating formulas]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#27): talking-head-production]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/talking-head-production</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/talking-head-production</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #27
Installs: 20
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Talking head video production with AI avatars, lipsync, and voiceover. Covers portrait requirements, audio quality, OmniHuman, PixVerse lipsync, Dia TTS. Use for: spokesperson videos, course content, social media, presentations, demos. Triggers: talking head, avatar video, lipsync, lip sync, ai spokesperson, virtual presenter, ai presenter, omnihuman, talking avatar, video presenter, ai talking head, presenter video, ai face video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#28): prompt-engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/prompt-engineering</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/prompt-engineering</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #28
Installs: 20
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Master prompt engineering for AI models: LLMs, image generators, video models. Techniques: chain-of-thought, few-shot, system prompts, negative prompts. Models: Claude, GPT-4, Gemini, FLUX, Veo, Stable Diffusion prompting. Use for: better AI outputs, consistent results, complex tasks, optimization. Triggers: prompt engineering, how to prompt, better prompts, prompt tips, prompting guide, llm prompting, image prompt, ai prompting, prompt optimization, prompt template, prompt structure, effective prompts, prompt techniques]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#29): audit-website]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/squirrelscan/skills/audit-website</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:squirrelscan/skills/audit-website</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #29
Installs: 18
Source: squirrelscan/skills
Description: Audit websites for SEO, performance, security, technical, content, and 15 other issue cateories with 150+ rules using the squirrelscan CLI. Returns LLM-optimized reports with health scores, broken links, meta tag analysis, and actionable recommendations. Use to discover and asses website or webapp issues and health.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#30): obsidian-bases]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/kepano/obsidian-skills/obsidian-bases</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:kepano/obsidian-skills/obsidian-bases</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #30
Installs: 31
Source: kepano/obsidian-skills
Description: Create and edit Obsidian Bases (.base files) with views, filters, formulas, and summaries. Use when working with .base files, creating database-like views of notes, or when the user mentions Bases, table views, card views, filters, or formulas in Obsidian.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#31): receiving-code-review]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/receiving-code-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:obra/superpowers/receiving-code-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #31
Installs: 23
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when receiving code review feedback, before implementing suggestions, especially if feedback seems unclear or technically questionable - requires technical rigor and verification, not performative agreement or blind implementation]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#32): seo-content-brief]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/seo-content-brief</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/seo-content-brief</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #32
Installs: 18
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: SEO content brief creation with keyword research, search intent analysis, and content structure. Covers SERP analysis, heading hierarchy, word count targets, and internal linking strategy. Use for: content briefs, SEO writing, blog strategy, content planning, keyword targeting. Triggers: seo content brief, content brief, seo brief, keyword research, search intent, content strategy, blog brief, seo writing, content planning, keyword targeting, serp analysis, content outline, seo article, blog seo]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#34): ui-design-system]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/samhvw8/dot-claude/ui-design-system</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:samhvw8/dot-claude/ui-design-system</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #34
Installs: 29
Source: samhvw8/dot-claude
Description: React UI component systems with TailwindCSS + Radix + shadcn/ui. Stack: TailwindCSS (styling), Radix UI (primitives), shadcn/ui (components), React/Next.js. Capabilities: design system architecture, accessible components, responsive layouts, theming, dark mode, component composition. Actions: review, design, build, improve, refactor UI components. Keywords: TailwindCSS, Radix UI, shadcn/ui, design system, component library, accessibility, ARIA, responsive, dark mode, theming, CSS variables, component architecture, atomic design, design tokens, variant, slot, composition. Use when: building component libraries, implementing shadcn/ui, creating accessible UIs, setting up design systems, adding dark mode/theming, reviewing UI component architecture.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#35): nextjs-supabase-auth]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/sickn33/antigravity-awesome-skills/nextjs-supabase-auth</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:sickn33/antigravity-awesome-skills/nextjs-supabase-auth</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #35
Installs: 25
Source: sickn33/antigravity-awesome-skills
Description: Expert integration of Supabase Auth with Next.js App Router Use when: supabase auth next, authentication next.js, login supabase, auth middleware, protected route.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#36): convex]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/waynesutton/convexskills/convex</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:waynesutton/convexskills/convex</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #36
Installs: 25
Source: waynesutton/convexskills
Description: Umbrella skill for all Convex development patterns. Routes to specific skills like convex-functions, convex-realtime, convex-agents, etc.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#37): ui-ux-pro-max]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/likaia/nginxpulse/ui-ux-pro-max</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:likaia/nginxpulse/ui-ux-pro-max</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #37
Installs: 24
Source: likaia/nginxpulse
Description: UI/UX design intelligence. 50 styles, 21 palettes, 50 font pairings, 20 charts, 8 stacks (React, Next.js, Vue, Svelte, SwiftUI, React Native, Flutter, Tailwind). Actions: plan, build, create, design, implement, review, fix, improve, optimize, enhance, refactor, check UI/UX code. Projects: website, landing page, dashboard, admin panel, e-commerce, SaaS, portfolio, blog, mobile app, .html, .tsx, .vue, .svelte. Elements: button, modal, navbar, sidebar, card, table, form, chart. Styles: glassmorphism, claymorphism, minimalism, brutalism, neumorphism, bento grid, dark mode, responsive, skeuomorphism, flat design. Topics: color palette, accessibility, animation, layout, typography, font pairing, spacing, hover, shadow, gradient.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#38): file-name-wizard]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/cygnusfear/agent-skills/file-name-wizard</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:cygnusfear/agent-skills/file-name-wizard</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #38
Installs: 22
Source: cygnusfear/agent-skills
Description: Audit all filename and naming conventions in the codebase against AGENTS.md standards and common patterns. Use when user asks to check naming conventions, audit filenames, find naming inconsistencies, or validate file naming patterns.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#39): angular-component]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/analogjs/angular-skills/angular-component</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:analogjs/angular-skills/angular-component</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #39
Installs: 22
Source: analogjs/angular-skills
Description: Create modern Angular standalone components following v20+ best practices. Use for building UI components with signal-based inputs/outputs, OnPush change detection, host bindings, content projection, and lifecycle hooks. Triggers on component creation, refactoring class-based inputs to signals, adding host bindings, or implementing accessible interactive components.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#4): twitter-automation]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/twitter-automation</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/twitter-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #4
Installs: 74
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Automate Twitter/X with posting, engagement, and user management via inference.sh CLI. Apps: x/post-tweet, x/post-create (with media), x/post-like, x/post-retweet, x/dm-send, x/user-follow. Capabilities: post tweets, schedule content, like posts, retweet, send DMs, follow users, get profiles. Use for: social media automation, content scheduling, engagement bots, audience growth, X API. Triggers: twitter api, x api, tweet automation, post to twitter, twitter bot, social media automation, x automation, tweet scheduler, twitter integration, post tweet, twitter post, x post, send tweet]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#40): technical-blog-writing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/technical-blog-writing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/technical-blog-writing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #40
Installs: 21
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Technical blog post writing with structure, code examples, and developer audience conventions. Covers post types, code formatting, explanation depth, and developer-specific engagement patterns. Use for: engineering blogs, dev tutorials, technical writing, developer content, documentation posts. Triggers: technical blog, dev blog, engineering blog, technical writing, developer tutorial, tech post, code tutorial, programming blog, developer content, technical article, engineering post, coding tutorial, technical content]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#41): flux-image]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/flux-image</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/flux-image</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #41
Installs: 18
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Generate images with FLUX models (Black Forest Labs) via inference.sh CLI. Models: FLUX Dev LoRA, FLUX.2 Klein LoRA with custom style adaptation. Capabilities: text-to-image, image-to-image, LoRA fine-tuning, custom styles. Triggers: flux, flux.2, flux dev, flux schnell, flux pro, black forest labs, flux image, flux ai, flux model, flux lora]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#43): tailwind-design-system]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/wshobson/agents/tailwind-design-system</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:wshobson/agents/tailwind-design-system</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #43
Installs: 30
Source: wshobson/agents
Description: Build scalable design systems with Tailwind CSS, design tokens, component libraries, and responsive patterns. Use when creating component libraries, implementing design systems, or standardizing UI patterns.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#44): typescript-e2e-testing]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/bmad-labs/skills/typescript-e2e-testing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:bmad-labs/skills/typescript-e2e-testing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #44
Installs: 27
Source: bmad-labs/skills
Description: Complete E2E (end-to-end) and integration testing skill for TypeScript/NestJS projects using Jest, real infrastructure via Docker, and GWT pattern.

ALWAYS use this skill when user needs to:

**SETUP** - Initialize or configure E2E testing infrastructure:
- Set up E2E testing for a new project
- Configure docker-compose for testing (Kafka, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis)
- Create jest-e2e.config.ts or E2E Jest configuration
- Set up test helpers for database, Kafka, or Redis
- Configure .env.e2e environment variables
- Create test/e2e directory structure

**WRITE** - Create or add E2E/integration tests:
- Write, create, add, or generate e2e tests or integration tests
- Test API endpoints, workflows, or complete features end-to-end
- Test with real databases, message brokers, or external services
- Test Kafka consumers/producers, event-driven workflows
- Working on any file ending in .e2e-spec.ts or in test/e2e/ directory
- Use GWT (Given-When-Then) pattern for tests

**REVIEW** - Audit or evaluate E2E tests:
- Review existing E2E tests for quality
- Check test isolation and cleanup patterns
- Audit GWT pattern compliance
- Evaluate assertion quality and specificity
- Check for anti-patterns (multiple WHEN actions, conditional assertions)

**RUN** - Execute or analyze E2E test results:
- Run E2E tests
- Start/stop Docker infrastructure for testing
- Analyze E2E test results
- Verify Docker services are healthy
- Interpret test output and failures

**DEBUG** - Fix failing or flaky E2E tests:
- Fix failing E2E tests
- Debug flaky tests or test isolation issues
- Troubleshoot connection errors (database, Kafka, Redis)
- Fix timeout issues or async operation failures
- Diagnose race conditions or state leakage
- Debug Kafka message consumption issues

**OPTIMIZE** - Improve E2E test performance:
- Speed up slow E2E tests
- Optimize Docker infrastructure startup
- Replace fixed waits with smart polling
- Reduce beforeEach cleanup time
- Improve test parallelization where safe

Keywords: e2e, end-to-end, integration test, e2e-spec.ts, test/e2e, Jest, supertest, NestJS, Kafka, Redpanda, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis, docker-compose, GWT pattern, Given-When-Then, real infrastructure, test isolation, flaky test, MSW, nock, waitForMessages, fix e2e, debug e2e, run e2e, review e2e, optimize e2e, setup e2e]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#45): typescript-react-reviewer]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/dotneet/claude-code-marketplace/typescript-react-reviewer</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:dotneet/claude-code-marketplace/typescript-react-reviewer</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #45
Installs: 25
Source: dotneet/claude-code-marketplace
Description: Expert code reviewer for TypeScript + React 19 applications. Use when reviewing React code, identifying anti-patterns, evaluating state management, or assessing code maintainability. Triggers: code review requests, PR reviews, React architecture evaluation, identifying code smells, TypeScript type safety checks, useEffect abuse detection, state management review.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#46): tools-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-5/skills/tools-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-5/skills/tools-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #46
Installs: 22
Source: inference-sh-5/skills
Description: name: tools-ui]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#47): verification-before-completion]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/verification-before-completion</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:obra/superpowers/verification-before-completion</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #47
Installs: 22
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when about to claim work is complete, fixed, or passing, before committing or creating PRs - requires running verification commands and confirming output before making any success claims; evidence before assertions always]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#48): competitor-teardown]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/competitor-teardown</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/competitor-teardown</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #48
Installs: 16
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Structured competitive analysis with feature matrices, SWOT, positioning maps, and UX review. Covers research frameworks, pricing comparison, review mining, and visual deliverables. Use for: market research, competitive intelligence, investor decks, product strategy, sales enablement. Triggers: competitor analysis, competitive analysis, competitor teardown, market research, competitive intelligence, swot analysis, competitor comparison, market landscape, competitor review, competitive landscape, feature comparison, market positioning]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#49): security-requirement-extraction]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/wshobson/agents/security-requirement-extraction</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:wshobson/agents/security-requirement-extraction</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #49
Installs: 28
Source: wshobson/agents
Description: Derive security requirements from threat models and business context. Use when translating threats into actionable requirements, creating security user stories, or building security test cases.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#5): video-ad-specs]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-4/skills/video-ad-specs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-4/skills/video-ad-specs</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #5
Installs: 32
Source: inference-sh-4/skills
Description: Video ad creation with exact platform-specific specs for TikTok, Instagram, YouTube, Facebook, LinkedIn. Covers dimensions, duration limits, AIDA framework, and caption requirements. Use for: video ads, social media ads, paid media creative, video marketing, ad production. Triggers: video ad, social media ad, tiktok ad, instagram ad, youtube ad, facebook ad, linkedin ad, video creative, ad specs, paid media, video marketing, ad production, reels ad, stories ad, pre roll, bumper ad]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#50): reka-ui]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/onmax/nuxt-skills/reka-ui</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:onmax/nuxt-skills/reka-ui</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #50
Installs: 26
Source: onmax/nuxt-skills
Description: Use when building with Reka UI (headless Vue components) - provides component API, accessibility patterns, composition (asChild), controlled/uncontrolled state, virtualization, and styling integration. Formerly Radix Vue.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#7): vercel-react-best-practices]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/vercel-labs/agent-skills/vercel-react-best-practices</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:vercel-labs/agent-skills/vercel-react-best-practices</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #7
Installs: 184
Source: vercel-labs/agent-skills
Description: React and Next.js performance optimization guidelines from Vercel Engineering. This skill should be used when writing, reviewing, or refactoring React/Next.js code to ensure optimal performance patterns. Triggers on tasks involving React components, Next.js pages, data fetching, bundle optimization, or performance improvements.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#8): mastra]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/mastra-ai/skills/mastra</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:mastra-ai/skills/mastra</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #8
Installs: 39
Source: mastra-ai/skills
Description: Comprehensive guide for building AI applications with Mastra, the TypeScript AI framework for agents and workflows. Covers LLM agents with tools and memory, multi-step workflows with branching/parallel execution, storage backends (Postgres/LibSQL), RAG/vector search, and custom tool creation. Use when building conversational agents, automated workflows, RAG systems, or any Mastra TypeScript/JavaScript application. Includes 27+ production-ready code patterns, API verification guidance, troubleshooting, and best practices.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] New entry (#9): agent-browser]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-3/skills/agent-browser</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:new:inference-sh-3/skills/agent-browser</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Hot leaderboard.
Rank: #9
Installs: 63
Source: inference-sh-3/skills
Description: Browser automation for AI agents via inference.sh. Navigate web pages, interact with elements using @e refs, take screenshots, record video. Capabilities: web scraping, form filling, clicking, typing, drag-drop, file upload, JavaScript execution. Use for: web automation, data extraction, testing, agent browsing, research. Triggers: browser, web automation, scrape, navigate, click, fill form, screenshot, browse web, playwright, headless browser, web agent, surf internet, record video]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#48): marketing-ideas]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/coreyhaines31/marketingskills/marketing-ideas</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topTrending:new:coreyhaines31/marketingskills/marketing-ideas</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #48
Installs: 343
Source: coreyhaines31/marketingskills
Description: When the user needs marketing ideas, inspiration, or strategies for their SaaS or software product. Also use when the user asks for 'marketing ideas,' 'growth ideas,' 'how to market,' 'marketing strategies,' 'marketing tactics,' 'ways to promote,' or 'ideas to grow.' This skill provides 139 proven marketing approaches organized by category.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Trending] New entry (#49): verification-before-completion]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/verification-before-completion</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topTrending:new:obra/superpowers/verification-before-completion</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New entry in Trending leaderboard.
Rank: #49
Installs: 342
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when about to claim work is complete, fixed, or passing, before committing or creating PRs - requires running verification commands and confirming output before making any success claims; evidence before assertions always]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[All Time] Rank up (28 → 19): agent-tools]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/inference-sh-3/skills/agent-tools</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topAllTime:rank:inference-sh-3/skills/agent-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[All Time leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #28
Current rank: #19
Delta: +9
Installs: 14712 (prev 10937)
Source: inference-sh-3/skills
Description: Run 150+ AI apps via inference.sh CLI - image generation, video creation, LLMs, search, 3D, Twitter automation. Models: FLUX, Veo, Gemini, Grok, Claude, Seedance, OmniHuman, Tavily, Exa, OpenRouter, and many more. Use when running AI apps, generating images/videos, calling LLMs, web search, or automating Twitter. Triggers: inference.sh, infsh, ai model, run ai, serverless ai, ai api, flux, veo, claude api, image generation, video generation, openrouter, tavily, exa search, twitter api, grok]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (10 → 17): executing-plans]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/executing-plans</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:rank:obra/superpowers/executing-plans</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #10
Current rank: #17
Delta: -7
Installs: 33 (prev 25)
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when you have a written implementation plan to execute in a separate session with review checkpoints]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (13 → 18): requesting-code-review]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/requesting-code-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:rank:obra/superpowers/requesting-code-review</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #13
Current rank: #18
Delta: -5
Installs: 32 (prev 25)
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when completing tasks, implementing major features, or before merging to verify work meets requirements]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (28 → 42): skill-creator]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/anthropics/skills/skill-creator</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:rank:anthropics/skills/skill-creator</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #28
Current rank: #42
Delta: -14
Installs: 70 (prev 50)
Source: anthropics/skills
Description: Guide for creating effective skills. This skill should be used when users want to create a new skill (or update an existing skill) that extends Claude's capabilities with specialized knowledge, workflows, or tool integrations.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (5 → 16): writing-plans]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/writing-plans</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:rank:obra/superpowers/writing-plans</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #5
Current rank: #16
Delta: -11
Installs: 39 (prev 35)
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: Use when you have a spec or requirements for a multi-step task, before touching code]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Hot] Rank down (8 → 11): brainstorming]]></title>
            <link>https://skills.sh/obra/superpowers/brainstorming</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19T13:20:26.979Z:topHot:rank:obra/superpowers/brainstorming</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 13:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hot leaderboard rank change.
Previous rank: #8
Current rank: #11
Delta: -3
Installs: 63 (prev 57)
Source: obra/superpowers
Description: You MUST use this before any creative work - creating features, building components, adding functionality, or modifying behavior. Explores user intent, requirements and design before implementation.]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>